Generated by ai-sub version: 0.0.3
Config: (
"rpm": 5,
"tpm": 250000,
"model": "gemini-2.5-pro",
"thinking_budget": 24576,
"max_subtitle_chars": 60,
"num_processing_threads": 4,
"num_upload_threads": 4,
"split_seconds": 180
)
Prompt Template: You are an expert subtitling and transcription AI. Your primary task is to generate precise, contextually rich English and Japanese subtitles for the provided video content.
**Key Principles & Requirements:**
1.  **TIMING ACCURACY (ABSOLUTE HIGHEST PRIORITY):**
*   **Ensure the `start` and `end` timestamps for each subtitle entry are meticulously accurate.** Both must align perfectly with the *actual beginning and end of the spoken words* for that specific segment.
*   **CRITICAL: The `end` timestamp is frequently inaccurate and requires special attention.** It must precisely mark the *exact conclusion* of the spoken content for that subtitle entry.
*   Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
2.  **CRITICAL: Holistic Translation, Contextual Understanding & Comprehensive Analysis:**
*   **You ABSOLUTELY MUST watch the entire video thoroughly** to understand the visual context, speaker actions, and overall narrative.
*   **When a single logical sentence or phrase is split across multiple subtitle entries (e.g., due to timing or character limits), you MUST mentally combine these parts to understand the full, complete meaning before translating.**
*   **NEVER translate individual subtitle entries in isolation if they are part of a larger, continuous thought or sentence.** The translation for each entry must be a coherent and accurate part of the complete, overarching sentence.
*   Analyze *all* spoken dialogue in the video to produce highly accurate and complete transcriptions.
*   For songs or singing sections, prioritize on-screen lyrics in the video for subtitles over transcribing the singing.
*   If the audio is noisy or unclear, leverage *all* contextual cues (visuals from the video, surrounding dialogue) to infer and generate the most probable dialogue.
*   Utilize the comprehensive understanding gained from *watching the entire video* to enhance the accuracy of transcriptions, translations, and overall subtitle quality. This includes understanding nuances, resolving ambiguities, and ensuring the subtitle content aligns perfectly with what is happening visually.
*   **Example:**
*   Original Japanese: "なんでも打ち明けられるママにも" (Subtitle 1) + "言えないことも全部" (Subtitle 2)
*   Incorrect Translation (isolated): "You're like a mom I can confide anything in." + "Even things I can't say to anyone else."
*   Correct Translation (holistic): "I can confide everything," (Subtitle 1) + "everything I can't even tell my mum." (Subtitle 2)
3.  **Dual Language Provision & Translation Quality:**
*   Provide both English and Japanese subtitles for *all* spoken dialogue.
*   If the original dialogue is in English, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding Japanese translation.
*   If the original dialogue is in Japanese, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding English translation.
*   Ensure translations are culturally appropriate and maintain the original meaning, tone, and intent, taking into account the full context of the video and any split sentences.
4.  **Readability & Formatting:**
* Long sentences MUST be split into multiple, shorter subtitle entries, each with its own start and end time, for better readability on screen. Each subtitle entry (english and japanese) MUST be a maximum of (max_subtitle_chars) characters. Do not use newline characters within a single subtitle entry.
** Output Format **
* Your entire response must be a single JSON object.
* Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
** Example Output **
```json
((
"subtitles": [
"start": "00:00",
"end": "00:04",
"english": "Hello everyone, and welcome to our presentation.",
"japanese": "皆様、プレゼンテーションへようこそ。"
)),
((
"start": "00:05",
"end": "00:06",
"english": "Today, we'll be discussing the future of AI",
"japanese": "本日は、AIの未来について"
)),
((
"start": "00:06",
"end": "00:08",
"english": "and its impact on various industries worldwide.",
"japanese": "その影響について議論します。"
)),
((
"start": "00:09",
"end": "00:11",
"english": "It's a very important topic for all of us.",
"japanese": "これは私たち全員にとって非常に重要なテーマです。"
)),
((
"start": "00:11",
"end": "00:14",
"english": "We sincerely appreciate your attendance today.",
"japanese": "本日はご出席いただき誠にありがとうございます。"
))
]
```
これは究極の心理戦
This is the ultimate psychological warfare.
運と知略、そして覚悟が試されるゲーム
A game that tests your luck, strategy, and resolve.
1から12までのイス
Chairs numbered from 1 to 12.
相手がどのイスに座るかを読み切り、電流を仕掛けろ
Predict which chair your opponent will sit on and set a trap.
電流を避ければ得点
Dodge the current to score points.
電流をくらえば…
But if you're hit by the current...
それまでのポイントは全て没収
all your points up to that point are forfeited.
心理戦を制し、勝利を掴むのは誰だ！？
Who will conquer the mind games and seize victory?!
ホロライブ 電気イスゲーム！
Hololive Electric Chair Game!
さあ、始まりましたホロライブ電気イスゲーム！
Well, the Hololive Electric Chair Game has begun!
イェーイ！
Yay!
今回はこの5名でお送りします。
This time, these five will be your hosts.
イェーイ！
Yay!
あれ？なんか様子が変ですけども
Huh? Something seems a little off...
皆さん
Everyone...
心理戦は得意ですよね？
You're all good at mind games, right?
はい、得意です！
Yes, I'm great at them!
心理戦は得意だ！
I'm great at them!
得意なわけねえだろ！
Like hell I am!
オレ今足が震えてしょうがない
My legs won't stop shaking right now.
似合わなすぎるで震えてる人いるんだ
There's even someone here who's trembling.
でも今日、心理戦得意なメンバー集めたんですけども
Well, I gathered members who are good at mind games today,
そのメンバー見て本当に言えるのか？それが
but looking at you all, can you really say that?
一番弱い奴いんじゃねえか
It seems like the weakest one is here.
じゃあじゃあじゃあ、そんなみこさん
Well then, Miko,
この中で勝てそうな人いますか？
is there anyone here you think you can beat?
すいちゃんは、まあ、基本謎解きが好きでしょ？
Suichan likes to solve puzzles, right?
うちも好きですけど
I like them too.
人狼ゲームも好きでしょ？
And you like werewolf games, right?
デスゲームが好きですよね？
You like death games, right?
デスゲーム好きなの！？
You like death games!?
謎解きもめっちゃ行ってる
I go to a lot of puzzle-solving events.
まあフブさんは言わずもがな…
Well, as for Fubu-san, it goes without saying...
頭脳系でしょ？
You're the brainy type, right?
ウチがアホって言いたい？
Are you trying to say I'm an idiot?
ピンポン！ピンポン！ピンポーン！
Ding! Ding! Ding!
唯一安心できるかもしれないなって
You're the only one I might feel safe around.
すごいオブラートに包んだけどそれアホってことじゃね
She sugarcoated it, but doesn't that mean you're an idiot?
じゃあその大神ミオはどうです？この人なら勝てそうって人いますか？
How about Ookami Mio? Is there anyone you can beat?
うーん
Hmm.
うちはー
As for me...
うーん誰かな
Hmm, who could it be?
リリカかな
Maybe Ririka?
どう見てもみこ先輩の方が
No matter how I look at it, Miko-senpai is...
今なんか、すっごいいいリアクションとった
You just had a really good reaction.
もう帰らせていただきます！
I'm going home now!
ルール説明
Rule Explanation
1から12の数が書かれたイスに座り、その数をポイントとして獲得するゲームです。
This is a game where you sit on chairs numbered 1-12 and earn points.
相手が座るイスを予想し、電流を仕掛けます
You predict which chair your opponent will sit on and set a current.
電流を食らうとそれまでのポイント没収
If you're hit, you lose all your points.
8ラウンドが終わり、得点が多い方が勝ちとなりますが、
After 8 rounds, the player with the most points wins, but...
電流を3回食らうと即失格
get hit by the current three times and you're disqualified.
40ポイントを獲得した時点で即勝利となります
Also, the moment you reach 40 points, you win instantly.
はい、という事でですね、ま、今回電気イスゲームなんですけども
Yes, so, this is the Electric Chair Game, but...
電流の強さを把握していない
We don't know how strong the current is.
ちょっと分かんない
I don't really know.
実際痛いかどうかは知っとかないとだもんね
We need to know if it actually hurts, you know?
そうそうそうそう
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
ちょっと莉々華…
Hey, Ririka...
いやいやいやいや
No no no no.
アホじゃないですよ 何アホって言ってるんですか
I'm not an idiot. Why are you calling me an idiot?
罰ゲームの王ならやっぱりね
If you're the queen of penalty games, then of course...
そうだよ
Of course...
今日はMCだと思って来たのに!!
I came here today thinking I was the MC!!
どうして
What happened?
そうなんだよな なんかみこもさ台本見たらさ 莉々華はなんかMCとかやるのかなって
Yeah, when I saw the script, I thought, 'Oh, I guess Ririka is going to be the MC.'
思ったのにメンバーズ的にはね うん
Based on the members, yeah.
まあ頑張れよ
Well, do your best.
これがホロライブか
So this is hololive...
ということでじゃあ莉々華には試しに電気椅子に座ってもらいます
And with that, we'll have Ririka try sitting in the electric chair.
わかりました
Okay.
こえー
It's scary...
ちょっと莉々華このままだとやばいので
Okay Ririka, this isn't going to work as it is.
ハートベール 心のベールをかけて
Heart Veil. Put on a veil over your heart.
え、何それ
What do you mean?
どういうこと
What?
ビリビリを怖くない人間に生まれ変わろうと思う
I will be reborn as someone who is not afraid of shocks.
怖いんだけど
I'm scared!
何言ってんの
What are you talking about?
莉々華心書き換えることできるの
Ririka can rewrite her heart.
何言ってるの
What is she saying?
どうしちゃったの
What's gotten into you?
こんなおかしい奴だったの？
Were you always this weird?
私ならいける。怖くない。
I can do this. I'm not scared.
むしろ電気は私を幸せにする
In fact, electricity makes me happy.
いっちゃってる
She's lost it.
洗脳している自らを
I'm brainwashing myself...
え～！楽しみ～！電撃だって！わ～い！
Yay! I'm so excited! Electric shock! Whoopee!
うるさいなこいつ
She's so annoying!
大丈夫でしょ
I think it'll be fine.
すごいよ
That's great!
ということで、電気椅子準備できました
And with that, the electric chair is ready.
いやあああ
Noooo!
ベール
The veil... aah!
ベール剥がれてる
The veil, the veil is peeling off.
大丈夫大丈夫
I-it's okay, I'm okay.
心のベール
The heart's veil.
取り戻した
Okay, that's better.
楽しい
It's so fun.
じゃあ行きますよ
Okay, let's go.
わーい
Yay!
練習まで3,2,1 ポチ
Counting down... 3, 2, 1... click.
グワァァー！？
GWAAAAR!?
ええ！
Huh?!
なんかバチバチって音したよ！？
I heard a crackling sound!?
何か飛んでいった
Something flew off!
なんか音が
There was a sound.
キモチイ...!
It feels good...!
大丈夫なの
Are you okay?
なんて言った
What did you say?
おしりのベール
The butt's veil.
Butt's veil?
おしりの
The butt's veil...
どうでしたか感想？
How was it? Your thoughts?
わけわかんなくなってる
She's not making any sense.
先輩
Senpai...
みこ先輩が
Miko-senpai...
楽しみだ
I'm so excited!
今回のトーナメントですが A, Bが第1試合
For this tournament, A and B will face off in Match 1.
C, Dが第2試合を行い、勝者は決勝リーグに進みます
C and D will face off in Match 2. The winners will advance to the final league.
一方敗者は、特典が高かった方が Eと第3試合を行い、勝者は決勝リーグに進みます
The losers with the higher scores will face E in Match 3. The winner will also advance to the final league.
A, B, C, Dは負けても敗者復活の可能性がありますが Eは相手の手の内が分かった状態で戦えるのがアドバンテージですね
For A, B, C, and D, even if you lose, there's a chance to be revived. But E's advantage is being able to see their opponent's moves beforehand.
決勝リーグは予選で得点が一番高かったプレイヤーがシード権を獲得し決勝に
For the final league, the player with the highest score in the qualifiers will earn a seed and advance to the finals.
予選リーグ成績上位者のみ決勝リーグへの進出となります。
Only top players from the prelims advance to the finals.
ただし、敗者復活のプレイヤーにはシード獲得権利はありません。
But players from the revival match cannot earn a seed.
みこ先輩覚えました？
Miko-senpai, did you memorize it?
A、B、C、D、E...
ABCD...
覚えた。
Yes, I did!
お前バカにしてんのか？
Are you making fun of me?
じゃあね、みんな決まりましたか？
Okay, has everyone decided?
はい。- はい。じゃあ、行きますよ。
Yes. - Okay, here we go.
せーの、えー！
Ready, set, go!
ひでぇな。
So mean!
白上とみこさん決まり。
Shirakami and Miko-san are set!
やったー！
Yes!
せーの、えー！
Ready, set, go!
やばい。
Oh, no!
みんなはAで決まりました。
Everyone is decided with A.
最初はグー、じゃんけんぽい！
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
あー！すいちゃんがB！
Oh! Sui-chan is B!
じゃあ、ミオがEになりました。
Then, Mio is E.
はい、これでやっていこうと思います。
Okay, this is how we'll do it.
頑張りまーす！
Let's do our best!
頑張りましょう！
勝つぞー！
I'm going to win!
そうなるとは限らないかもしれないよ。
It might not turn out that way, you know.
予選リーグ第1試合は、星街すいせい対一条リリカ！
The first match of the prelims is Hoshimachi Suisei vs. Ichijou Ririka!
うわー、負けらんねえ！
Wow, I can't lose!
意気込みを一言ありますか？星街。
Any words of encouragement? Hoshimachi.
私は...堅実に...
I'll...play it safe.
そ...それだけですか？
I-is that all?
終わりです、はい。
That's it. Yes.
分かりました。では、一条リリカ。
Okay. Next, Ichijou Ririka.
すいちゃん先輩。そのケツいただきますよ(?)
Sui-chan-senpai. I'm taking your ass.
だめ。- だめなの？
No. - No?
もらえなかった。
I couldn't get it.
ということで、お互い気合は入ってるんですかな？
So, are you both fired up?
なんとですね、ここでちょっと主催からですね、連絡がございまして、
Well, we just heard from the organizers.
このゲーム、優勝した方には商品があるということなんです。
The winner of this game will get a prize.
えー！商品！
What? A prize!
100万円とか1,000万円とか1億円とか...
Like 1 million yen, 10 million yen, or 100 million yen...
優勝した方のご自宅に届いてからのお楽しみだそうなんです。
It's a surprise until it's delivered to the winner's house.
いらんもんだったらどうしよう。
What if it's something I don't want?
期待してください。
Please look forward to it.
それではですね、先行後攻決めてもらうんですけども、ここから駆け引きが始まってますよ。
Now, you'll decide who goes first, and the mind games begin.
じゃんけんでもいいですし、話し合いでも構いません。それでは先行後攻決めてください。
You can use janken or discuss it. Please decide.
最初に仕掛けさせてください。
Let me set the trap first.
ええー！？
What?!
どうしよっかな。
What should I do?
最初に仕掛けさしてください。
Let me set the trap first.
その心は？
And why is that?
いや、えっと、なんか...
Well, um, it's just...
神からお告げがあって。
I had a revelation from god.
ミオさんはどっちが負けると思いますか？
Mio-san, who do you think will lose?
さすがにリリカじゃないかなって思うけどな。
I'd have to say it's probably not Ririka, though.
すいちゃん負けるんじゃない？
Sui-chan's gonna lose, don't you think?
ええ？！すいちゃん意外と運ないから。
What?! Sui-chan's surprisingly unlucky.
「こっちだと思うんだよね。」
"I think it's this one."
「痛ってええええ！？」
"Owwwww!?"
それ願望だろ？
That's just wishful thinking, isn't it?
願望。
Wishful thinking.
そうなってほしい、頼む～！
I want it to happen, please!
いいですよ。- あ、ほんと！？
Okay. - Oh, really?!
もう爆速で40ポイント取って、抜けさせていただきます。
I'll just get 40 points at lightning speed and get out of here.
それはどうかな。
I wonder about that.
ということで決まりましたがね。では、先行がリリカ、後攻がすいちゃんということで、
So it's decided. Ririka will go first, and Sui-chan will go second.
はい、決まりました。ではまず先行のリリカはですね、えー、すいちゃんが仕掛けますので、では、ご退室をお願いします。
Okay, it's decided. So first, Ririka, Sui-chan will set the trap, so please exit the room.
読んだ。ふん。
I've read you. Hmph.
では星街。座る椅子、予想してください。
Alright, Hoshimachi. Guess which chair she'll sit on.
そうですね。まあ、ちょっと…
Right. Well...
実はまだ莉々華への解像度が高くない
Honestly, my 'read' on Ririka isn't that sharp yet.
ところはありますね。
That's just how it is.
かなり遊びに行ったりとかしてるんですけど
We've gone out to play quite a bit, but...
堅実に行くのか…
Will she play it safe...?
その、一気に12ポイント狙いにいくくらい
or is she bold enough to go for 12 points all at once?
大胆なのか、ちょっとまだ分かってない。
I'm still not quite sure about that.
でも一旦、12は取られたくないし、
But for now, I don't want her to take 12.
守りと様子見で
So, to be defensive and see what happens,
12に仕掛けとこうかなっていう。
I think I'll set up chair 12.
12にしたの？
She chose 12?
12にしてる。即ぎめじゃん。
She chose 12. That was a quick decision.
でも「12はないんじゃない？」って言って座る可能性も全然あるよね？
But she might say, "It's not 12," and sit, right?
みこもないと思うけど、そこまでバカじゃないだろ。
I don't think so either. She's not that stupid.
これで12座ったらちょっとアホ認定されちゃうかも。
If she sits on 12, she might be certified as a dummy.
電流を食らわせることができた場合、その椅子はキープされますが、
If you successfully electrocute your opponent, that chair is kept.
獲得された場合は、椅子は撤収されます。
But if they claim it, the chair is removed.
では、一条莉々華、座る椅子を決めてください。
Alright, Ichijou Ririka, please choose a chair to sit on.
じゃあちょっと…
Okay, well...
1から順番に数字全部言ってもらっていいですか？
Can you say all the numbers in order starting from 1?
声の震えをね？
To hear the tremble in my voice?
いち…
O-one.
はい。
Yes.
いや、全部震えないでください。
Hey, don't tremble on all of them!
言っちゃだめだったのかこれ。声の震えを聞くの言っちゃだめだったか。
Oh, was I not supposed to say that? That you're listening.
よん。
F-four.
ご…。
Fi-five.
なんかおもろ。
This is kinda funny.
なんかごまかそうとしてるね。
She's trying to bluff.
何やらされてんだ。
What are you making me do?
すいちゃん先輩が仕掛けたのは、5番ですね。
The one Suichan-senpai set up is... number 5.
私は12に座る。
I'll sit on 12.
かかってこいやぁ！
Bring it on!
5番に仕掛けたから私は12に座りますって言ってた！
She said, "You set up 5, so I'm sitting on 12!"
あぁー！
Aaaah!
はい。では決まりましたので、電流のスイッチを押してください。
Okay. Since the choice is made, please press the switch.
はい。
Yes.
（悲鳴）
(Screaming)
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
マジ？
For real?
すいちゃん気持ちいいやろな今！
Suichan must be feeling great right now!
痛い。
That hurts.
おしりが…。
My butt...
負け犬がぁ！！
You loser!!
おしりが…うそだろ…。
My butt... You've gotta be kidding me...
ということで一条は…。
And so, Ichijou...
負けねえよ！
I'm not gonna lose!
得点はなしです。
No points are awarded.
絶対に12じゃないと思ってどっしり構えてたのに！
I was so sure it wasn't 12, I was totally ready!
これ莉々華アホや。
Ririka's a dummy for that.
おもろすぎだろ！
That's too funny!
それでは、一条莉々華、仕掛ける椅子を決めてください。
Alright then, Ichijou Ririka, please choose a chair to set up.
分かりました…。
Alright...
この両尻にかけて…。
I'll bet both my butt cheeks...
絶対にすいちゃん先輩にビリビリを与えたい。
I will absolutely zap Suichan-senpai.
いやでもすいちゃん先輩が3とか8とかに座ったら、それはすいちゃん先輩じゃない気がするんだよな。
But if Suichan sat on 3 or 8, that wouldn't feel like her.
よし。
Alright.
これでいく。
I'll go with this one.
じゃあ、仕掛けてください。
Okay, please set the trap.
どうぞ。
Go ahead.
後攻 星街すいせい。座る椅子、決めてください。
Next up, Hoshimachi Suisei. Please decide which chair to sit on.
お願いします。
Please!
うわ、土下座。
Whoa, she's groveling.
教えてください！
Tell me, please!
すいちゃん先輩に…
To Suichan-senpai...
あの星街すいせいが頭を下げて…
The Hoshimachi Suisei is bowing her head...
土下座をしてる！！
She's groveling!!
情けない…すいちゃん…
How pathetic... Suichan...
こんなところ見たくなかった！！
I didn't want to see this!!
こっから...
From here...
こっから…
こっち側に仕掛けました。
I set it on this side.
あ、こっち？
Oh, this side?
こっち？
This side?
こっからこっち？
From here to this side?
本当ですか…？
Are you sure...?
はい。
Yes.
本当です。
It's true.
今、ちょっと感覚をね…感覚をね、お尻からの波動をね。
I'm just trying to get a feel... from the vibrations from my butt.
波動…
Vibrations...
まあ、ここは無いだろう。
Well, it's probably not this one.
おお！
Oh!
では、リリカさん。
Okay, Ririka-san.
行くぜ。
Here I go.
いや！
No!
では、お願いします。
Okay, please proceed.
ビリビリ攻撃！
Electric shock attack!
セーフ！
SAFE!
ということで、星街すいせい、11ポイント獲得！
And with that, Hoshimachi Suisei gets 11 points!
こんなバカな！
This can't be!
うわあ、崩れ落ちてる。
Wow, she's collapsing.
惜しかったな。
That was close.
惜しかったね。
It was close.
では、星街すいせい、座る椅子を予想してください。
Now, Hoshimachi Suisei, please predict which chair she will sit on.
いや、まあここまで12が2連続で来てる。
Well, 12 has come up twice in a row now.
「次は12じゃないだろう」みたいな思考になるんじゃないかみたいなところもあり
She might think, "It won't be 12 next time,"...
ただビビって座らないかのどっちかなのか
or she'll be too scared to sit there. It's one or the other.
じゃ12行っときますか。
I'll go with 12.
行くかな？
Will she go for it?
そこまでバカじゃないんじゃない？
She's not that stupid, is she?
そこまでアホじゃないよ。
She's not that much of an idiot.
では、一条莉々華、座る椅子、決めてください。
Now, Ichijo Ririka, please decide which chair to sit on.
はい。もう私は決めてきました、どの椅子に座るか。
Yes. I've already decided which chair to sit on.
そうなんですね。
Oh, you have?
なので一つだけ質問します。
So I'll just ask one question.
すいちゃん先輩…12番に仕掛けました？
Suichan-senpai... did you trap number 12?
仕掛けました。
I did.
あっ、仕掛けたの！？
Oh, you did!?
12なんだ。
It's 12.
うん、12なんだ。
Yeah, it's 12.
12狙いなんだやっぱ。
She's aiming for 12 after all.
もう一回聞きますね。
I'll ask one more time.
ちょっと目をよく見てください。
Please look closely at my eyes.
すいちゃん先輩、12番に仕掛けましたか？
Suichan-senpai, did you trap number 12?
仕掛けました。
I did.
なるほど。
I see.
分かりました。
I get it.
すいちゃん先輩は12に仕掛けてないと思います。
Suichan-senpai, I don't think you trapped number 12.
なぜなら今…
Because just now...
右上を見ましたね？
You looked up and to the right, didn't you?
調べたんです。
I looked it up.
人は嘘をつくとき、つい右上を見てしまうって。
When people lie, they tend to look up and to the right.
もう笑ってますやん。
She's already laughing.
すいちゃん先輩が同じ記事を読んでなければ、12は安全なはず。
Unless Suichan-senpai read the same article, 12 should be safe.
じゃ、お座りください。
Okay, please take a seat.
行くぞ。
Here I go.
いや、しかもな、すいちゃん先輩がそんな２回連続で12に置くわけがないしな。
Besides, there's no way Suichan-senpai would pick 12 two times in a row.
ではかかってこいや！
Alright, bring it on!
リリちゃん、お願いします。
Go ahead, Ririka-chan.
左尻に体重をかけよう。
I'll put my weight on my left butt cheek.
いや、悔しいなあ。
Man, this is frustrating.
ああ！
Aah!
なんでだよー！
Why me?!
見ていたのかあの記事を…！
You saw that article, didn't you?!
見ていたさ。
Of course I saw it.
意図的だったのか！！
You did that on purpose!!
あの記事を残しておけば
If I left that article up,
私が右上を見たとき
when I looked up and to the right,
嘘だって思うだろ？
you'd think I was lying, right?
そう思った。
I knew it.
心理戦がうますぎる！
You're too good at mind games!
負けた…
I lost...
ああ、お尻が痛い…
Aah, my butt hurts...
右尻も
My right cheek...
右尻も左尻も痛い…
Both my right and left cheeks hurt...
ちょっと待って
Hold on.
勝てないって…
I can't win...
強すぎるって
She's too strong.
勝てないよ…
I can't win...
もうやだ！帰らせていただく！！
I've had enough! I'm going home!!
帰らせていただく
I'm going home.
帰りたいよ…
I wanna go home...
もうやだ！
I've had enough!
でも40P取られたら負けなんでしょ？
But if you get 40 points, I lose, right?
どうしよう。
What should I do?
10ポイント系のやつでもこれ座られてなくなっちゃったら困るもんな。
The 10-point ones... if she sits on them and they disappear, I'll be in trouble.
12番。
Number 12.
でも魔の12番は…なくすか。
But the dreaded number 12... should I get rid of it?
いや…
No...
今度こそ。
This time for sure.
ここに仕掛ける！
I'll set the trap here!
完璧。
Perfect.
魂を込めて…
With all my soul...
オレはここに頓挫する。
I will squat right here.
では後攻、星街すいせい。座る椅子決めてください。
Now for the second player, Hoshimachi Suisei. Please choose your chair.
なんすかこのポーズは。
What is this pose?
これはもう威嚇態勢。
This is my intimidation stance.
威嚇態勢？
Intimidation stance?
もう何も心を読まれないという強い…
A strong stance so you can't read my mind...
リリカさん、12は仕掛けましたか？
Ririka-san, did you booby-trap 12?
12は仕掛けてない。
I didn't trap 12.
10は仕掛けましたか？
Did you trap 10?
10も仕掛けてない。
I didn't trap 10 either.
9は？
What about 9?
9は仕掛けた。
I trapped 9.
She trapped 9.
9に仕掛けたというね。
She says she trapped 9.
ブラフをね？これが看抜かれるかどうか
Is it a bluff? Can she see through it?
なんかリリカ、素直そうなんだよな。
Somehow, Ririka seems honest.
いや、すごいひねくれてます。
No, I'm very twisted.
もう今リリカの心の中には
Right now, inside my heart,
すごい幼虫とか飼ってる(?)
I'm raising a huge larva or something (?)
任せてください(?)
Leave it to me (?)
いやでもね、
Well, but,
安牌でいってもいいかな。今勝ってるし。
Maybe I should play it safe. I'm winning right now.
あと一回電撃を食らわせれば私は勝てるわけだから。
If I can shock her just one more time, I'll win.
逃げるんですか？すいちゃん先輩。
Are you running away, Suichan-senpai?
いいんですか？そんな
Is that really okay?
これは仁義なき戦い。
This is a battle without honor or humanity.
てことは、ここに仕掛けたりなんかしてないですもんね、絶対。
Which means you definitely didn't trap this one, right?
ここで。
Right here.
うん。
Yeah.
では。
Alright then.
いいんだな。
Are you sure?
リリカさん、お願いします。
Ririka-san, please.
魂、電撃！
Soul, electric shock!
セーフ！
Safe!
星街すいせい、6ポイントゲット！
Hoshimachi Suisei gets 6 points!
星街すいせい、座るイスを予想して座ってください。
Hoshimachi Suisei, predict the chair she'll sit on, and please take a seat.
ここかなり悩みどこですね。
This is a tough one.
「もうさすがに12はないだろう」と思うか
Either she thinks, 'there's no way it's 12 again,'
もう12にビビるかどっちかだけど
or she'll get scared of 12. It's one of those.
10とか座るんじゃない？
I think she'll sit on 10 or something.
なるほどな。
I see.
あ、たしかに。
Yeah, that makes sense.
莉々華は10か12な気がするよ、みこも。
I think Ririka will pick 10 or 12, too.
まあね。
Well, yeah...
先攻、一条莉々華、座るイス選んでください。
First up, Ichijou Ririka. Please choose a chair to sit on.
はい。すいちゃん先輩、私のことアホだと思ってますね？
Yes. Suichan-senpai... You think I'm an idiot, don't you?
思ってないよ。
No, I don't.
本当かなぁ...？
Really...?
また莉々華が12に座ると思ったんじゃないですか！？
You thought Ririka would sit on 12 again, didn't you!?
思ってないよ。
I didn't think that.
莉々華はそこまで甘くない…
Ririka's not that naive...
そこも読まれてる...ｗ
She's reading that too...!
それも読まれてるんじゃないの...？ｗ
She's even reading *that* part, isn't she...?
もう...一人だけの尻じゃないんだ。
This isn't just one person's butt anymore.
2つの尻が...合わさってんだ！
Two butts have come together!
みんなの尻があるもんね？
Everyone's butts are on the line.
みんなの尻なんだ！！
It's everyone's butt!!
俺は10番に座る！
I'll sit on number 10!
10番か。
Number 10, huh?
来い！
Come on!
では、お願いします。
Okay, please proceed.
ーあっ！ーえっ！？
- Aah! - What?!
ー嘘！
- It's a lie!
よっしゃー！
Yes!
実に分かりやすかったよ君は。
You were really easy to read.
10に座るって思ったんですか？
Did you think I was going to sit on 10?
思いましたね。くそ！
Yes, I did. Damn it...
なんで？
Why?
さすがにここまで連続で12来たら、12にビビるかなとは思いましたね。
I thought if 12 came up this many times in a row, you'd get scared of it.
ビビってない!!
I wasn't scared!!
読まれないように10にしただけだ!!
I just picked 10 so you couldn't read me!!
ということで、改めまして初戦、勝った星街すいせいさん、一言どうぞ。
So, once again, the winner of the first match is Hoshimachi Suisei! A word, please.
いや、これ、1回も今日、電気イス座りません。
Well... I haven't sat in the electric chair even once today.
じゃあ...
Well then...
第1試合・第2試合の敗者のうち得点が高い方が敗者復活の権利を獲得する。0ポイント…
Among the losers of the first and second matches, the one with the higher score gets the right to a repechage... but with zero points...
そうです よね。みこ先輩、待ってますね。高みで。
That's right... Miko-senpai, I'm waiting for you... from the top.
お前、なんだよ！お前！どういうことだよ！みこのこと。
You little...! What do you mean by that? How dare you look down on Miko!
みこ先輩 対 ふぶき先輩です！
Miko-senpai vs. Fubuki-senpai!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いやー、ちょっと莉々華があんまりにも
I can't believe Ririka lost so badly...
3連発で当たるなんての見せられたらね...。頑張るしかないなとは。
getting it wrong three times in a row... I'll have to try hard for her sake.
大丈夫です、みこ先輩。すぐ同じ景色見れますからね。
Don't worry, Miko-senpai. You'll see the same sight soon.
お前、何言ってんのさっきからよ、お前！
What have you been saying this whole time!?
はい、ということで、決めますか。はい、先攻後攻決めてくださいよ。
Alright, then. Let's decide who goes first and second.
どっちがいいですか？
Which would you like?
え、先攻が先に座る方ですよね。
The first player sits first, right?
いや、みこ後攻が。
Yeah, Miko will go second.
あ、仕掛ける側がいい？
Oh, you'll be the one setting the trap?
はい、いいですよ。じゃあ。
Yes, that's fine.
あ、いいの？はい、全然。
Oh, are you sure? Okay then.
座らないから、みこさんの方。
The one not sitting? Okay, Miko-san, your turn.
なめてる みんななめてる 怖い
They're underestimating me. Everyone is. It's scary.
じゃあね 先攻はフブキ先輩 そして後攻はみこ先輩となりました
Okay, Fubuki-senpai will go first. And Miko-senpai will go second.
はい では先攻のフブキ先輩はご退室ください
Yes. Fubuki-senpai, who is going first, please leave the room.
バイバーイ
Bye-bye!
何かな
What should I pick...
まあでも 最初は
Well, for the first one...
まあ 10から12の3つのどれかだと思うんですけど
Well, I think it's one of the three from 10 to 12, but...
一旦10とか9に座ってもおかしくない
It wouldn't be strange to sit on 10 or 9 for now.
おかしくはない
It's not strange.
すいちゃんも1発目11に座って12回避してた
Sui-chan also sat on 11 for her first turn and avoided 12.
確かにそうだった
That's true.
10…いやここで12取られたらまずいなぁ
10... No, it'd be bad if she takes 12 here.
12 12にします はい
12! I'll choose 12. Yes.
先攻 白上フブキ
First turn, Shirakami Fubuki.
座る椅子を決めてください
Please decide which chair to sit on.
はい うーん
Yes. Hmm.
さあどうするんだよ
Now, what will she do?
みこさん多分12に仕掛けたっしょ
Miko-san probably set it to 12.
12じゃない 本当…？
It's not 12. Really?
12じゃないよ
It's not 12.
多分ね みこさんの考え的には
From Miko-san's point of view,
フブさんはギャンブラーだから12を取るだろうと思いつつも
she'd think I'm a gambler and would go for 12.
でも いや…10かなってなるんだけども
But then she'd reconsider, maybe 10.
でも12このまま行かれたらやばいよなっていう気持ちで
But feeling it'd be bad if I took 12,
多分そのまま12に仕掛けてるんで11
she probably just set it to 12. So I'll choose 11.
ああそのね
Ah, that kind of...
完全に読まれてますね これ すごい
She's been completely read. Amazing.
だって10か12で迷ってたもんね？
Because she was hesitating between 10 and 12, right?
そうそうそうそう
Yes, yes, yes.
いいですね 11で本当にいいですね
Is that okay? Are you sure about 11?
大丈夫です 11でお願いします 絶対仕掛けてんの12
It's fine. Please go with 11. She definitely set it to 12.
それじゃあ
Alright then,
行くよ！せーの！パチ！
here I go! Ready, set, zap!
セーフ！イエーイ！
SAFE! YAY!
うっそ 12… うわー！くそー！
No way, 12... Argh, damn it!
バーカ！
Idiot!
バカ
Idiot.
Baka!
最大煽りきました
That's the ultimate taunt.
煽られてます
She's being taunted.
うーん どうかな
Hmm, I wonder.
でもあえて12にしとく
But I'll deliberately set it to 12.
取られたくないっていうのは確かにあるので白上が一歩リードしてるので
It's true that I don't want it to be taken, and I'm one step ahead,
じゃあ10
Then 10...
こっちにしとこ よし
I'll go with this one. Okay.
後攻さくらみこ ではみこ先輩 座る椅子を選んでください
Second turn, Sakura Miko. Okay, Miko-senpai, please choose your chair.
はい
Yes.
12ですか？
Is it 12?
12ではないね
It's not 12.
10 うん
10. Uh-huh.
9.
9じゃないね だって10に仕掛けたもん
Not 9. Because I set it to 10.
8.
10に仕掛けたつってんだろ
I told you I set it to 10.
うーん
Hmm...
ここは7
Here, it's 7.
お 7にしちゃうんだ
Oh. She's going with 7.
堅実に
Playing it safe.
ほら見てください ビビってます
Look, she's scared.
ビビってるね これ！
She's scared!
完全にビビってます
Completely scared.
相当ビビってる
Very scared.
自分の尻が惜しいんだな これ
She really wants to save her own skin.
終わったら終わりだよ 電気浴びたらライフ1削れるよ
If it's over, it's over. Getting shocked reduces your life by 1.
そうですね
That's right.
でも7には仕掛けてないだろ
But she wouldn't set it to 7.
では 決まったようですので
Well, since you've decided,
怖い！
Scary!
座っていただいて
please sit down.
怖い
Scary.
怖い！ どうしよ…
Scary! What should I do...
あ、座るか
Oh, is she gonna sit?
みこさんらしいよね
That's so Miko.
あ
Ah.
7にします
I'll go with 7.
はい
Okay.
今のは、今のはそんな風に
That one, that was... like that.
やだ、怖いよ
No, it's scary!
では、電流装置押してください。
Now, please press the button.
みこさん！
Miko-san!
いけ！
Go!
だー！
Yay!
おおー！すごい！
Ooh! Amazing!
くっそー
Damn it!
今どこにあったの！？12か？
Where was it?! 12?
12。
12.
危ねえ。まあ、取られたくないってのはあったのでね。
That was close. Well, I didn't want you to get it.
そうですね。
That's right.
これ
This...
では、みこ先輩、フブキ先輩が座る椅子を予想してください。
Okay, Miko-senpai, please guess which chair Fubuki-senpai will sit on.
や、みこさん的には次は
Well, for Miko, next time...
次は12か10だと思うんだけども
I think it's either 12 or 10.
いや、10。
No, 10.
10です。
It's 10.
それでは電流装置を
Then, the button...
はい。
Yes.
それでは座る椅子を決めてください。
Alright, please choose a chair to sit on.
さあ、どうする。
Now, what to do?
さあ、どうしようかな、どうしようかな。
What should I do, what should I do?
多分後半戦、後半には仕掛けてそうなんだよね。
She'll probably set a trap in the second half.
だから割とこっちの前半部分は安心だと思いながらも
So I feel like the first half is relatively safe, but...
待ってる間に決めてたのは12に座りたいんだよね
while I was waiting, I decided I wanted to sit on 12.
そう、でも12にみこさんは仕掛けるかな
Yeah, but would Miko set a trap on 12?
９？
9?
９じゃない。
Not 9.
10？
10?
10じゃない。
Not 10.
じゃあ12？
Then 12?
12じゃない。
Not 12.
え、じゃあどこに仕掛けたの？
Then where did you set it?
分からない。なんで分かんなくなってんじゃん。
I don't know. How could you not know?
みこさん顔に出ちゃうから。
Because it shows on your face, Miko-san.
みこさんとの交渉は受け付けませんよ。
I won't accept any negotiations with Miko-san.
なんでやねん、そんな。
Why not?
受け付けませんよ。
I won't accept them.
でも、みこさんは多分なんか無難にこの辺選んでそうなんだよね。
But Miko would probably make a safe choice around here.
無難にね。そうそうそう。
A safe choice, huh? Yeah, yeah.
なんか２回連続12は選びそうにないので。
She's unlikely to choose 12 twice in a row, so...
ビビってんのか？ビビってんのか？
Are you scared? Are you scared?
ビビらずにじゃあ12だよ。
If I'm not scared, then it's 12.
おい。
Hey!
本当に？ビビらずに12なの？本当にいいんだね？
Really? 12 without fear? Are you sure?
言ったら変えねえんだ、12に２回連続は行かねえよ。
I won't change my mind. I won't go for 12 twice.
行かねえ。
I won't.
あ、怖い、怖い。
Oh, it's scary, scary!
いいのね？いいのね？
You're sure? You're sure?
いいよ。それでは電気、3、2、1...
I'm sure. Alright then, electricity! 3, 2, 1...
だーっ！セーフ！
Yay! Safe!
12にやられたー。
Got me with 12!
うわー、いや、これはなかなか難しいですよ。
Wow. Well, this is quite difficult.
みこさん。
Miko-san.
これみこち高得点狙っていかないと、
Mikochi has to aim for a high score,
もしくはフブキにぶち当てるからね。
or she has to hit Fubuki.
うん。
Yeah.
では、みこ先輩が座る椅子を予想してみてください。
Now, guess which chair Miko-senpai will sit on.
そうだなー、じゃあ。
Let's see. Then...
この辺には座りたいよね、みこさん的には。
She'll want to sit around here.
なので、
So...
10。仕掛けます。
10. I'll set a trap.
はい。おし。
Okay. Done.
みこさんは多分1〜6に座るんじゃない？
Miko-san will probably sit on 1 to 6, don't you think?
なんかそんな感じするよね。
It feels like that, doesn't it?
取りに行かずに
Instead of going for points,
電撃をフブさんに食らわせることを大前提とするんじゃない？
isn't her goal to zap Fubuki instead?
大前提とするんじゃない？
Isn't that the big assumption?
はいはいはい。っていう脳みそがあるかどうか。
Right, right, right. Whether they have the brain for that or not.
後攻さくらみこ
Second Turn: Sakura Miko
なるほどね。
I see.
座る椅子を、決めてください。
The chair you'll sit on. Please decide.
どうしようかなぁ。
What should I do?
でもみこさんはもうここらへんは取りに行かないと予想されているはず。
But I'm sure they're expecting me not to go for these ones.
もうフブさん23点も取っている。
Fubuki already has 23 points.
みこはまだ8点なわけ。
And I only have 8 points.
7点な？
7 points, right?
いいですね。思考ちゃんと読んでますね。
Nice. She's reading the situation properly.
7点な？
7 points, right?
7点だ。
It is 7 points.
ほんとだ。うん。
You're right. Yeah.
いやーでもここら辺で10は欲しいけどなー。
But I really want the 10 around here.
リリカは堂々と座ってたなぁ。
Ririka sat down with such confidence.
後輩は堂々としてたよ。
My kouhai was so poised.
みこ先輩、待ってますよ。高みで。
Miko-senpai, I'll be waiting for you. At the top.
9… 待って、8×8＝16
9... Wait, 8 x 8 = 16
8×8＝64な？
8 x 8 = 64, right?
ん？
Huh?
8×8＝16？
8 times 8 is 16?
なんなんなんそれ？
What is that?
アホ計算やめて急にｗ
Stop with the dumb math all of a sudden lol
8を8回繰り返してどうすんの？
What're you doing, repeating 'eight' eight times?
ええ、9だ。
Okay, 9 it is.
いいの？
Are you sure?
9にする。
I'll go with 9.
いいの？
Are you sure?
9にする。
I'll go with 9.
どうぞ。はい。
Go ahead. Okay.
ではお座りになりましたので、
Now that she's seated,
電撃をどうぞ。
please activate the shock.
こーい！
Bring it!
バイバイ。
Bye-bye.
SAFE
どこで鳴った今？
Where did that sound come from?
くそー！10だよ！
Damn it! It was 10!
あぶねー！
That was close!
ああー！
*screams of relief*
くっそー！
Damn it!
おっしゃー！
Alright!
おおー、じゃあみこ先輩は16ポイントになりましたね。
Ooh, so Miko-senpai now has 16 points.
16ポイント。
16 points.
まだまだまくれる。
It's still possible to make a comeback.
まだまだまくれるだろうフブキなら。
You can do it, Fubuki.
さあ、どうかな？
Well, we'll see.
まだ決まってない。
It's not over yet.
じゃあ、選ぶんだよ。
Well, you have to choose.
あ、そうだったそうだった。みこさんが選ぶんだった。
Oh, right, right. It's my turn to choose.
もうこんなにためできないよー。
I can't hesitate this much.
えーっと。
Um...
まあでもフブさん10…。
Well, Fubuki... 10...
いや、もう余裕ぶっこいて6とかに来る可能性はありますな。
No, she might act all cocky and go for something like 6.
多分みこさん何も考えずに置いた方が良いかも。
Maybe Miko should just place it without thinking.
ｗ
*laughs*
ランダム制？そう。
Randomly? Yeah.
当てたいなあ。
I want to get her.
うわー。
Ugh...
でも10を選ばずに10で当てられて得点取られたら怖いしな。
But if I don't pick 10 and she gets points, that'd be scary.
10にする。
I'll choose 10.
もう一度10な。
10 again.
では設置お願いします。
Please set the trap.
よし。
Alright.
先攻 白上フブキ
First Turn: Shirakami Fubuki
そうだなあ。
Let's see.
なんとなくだけどみこさんは、
I have a feeling Miko-san...
もう自分が10を取りたいが故に10に仕掛けてそうなので、
set the trap on 10 because she wants it for herself, so...
※心を読まれた人の顔
*The face of someone whose mind has been read*
こっちはポイントで勝ってるので、
I'm winning on points, so...
まあまあでも取られたくないとこで言うとそうだなあ。
a spot I don't want taken would be... well...
まあチャンスとかあるしなあ。
there's a chance space...
無難に4とか言っとくか。
I'll just play it safe and say 4.
仕掛けてないっしょ、どうせ。
She wouldn't have set it there anyway.
無難に4！
Playing it safe with 4!
まあ4は仕掛けてないよ。びびってんのかフブキ！
Yeah, she wouldn't set it on 4. Are you scared, Fubuki?!
余裕だよ。ポイントがある。
This is easy. I have the points.
ブブテーな。びびりしてんのか？
You're chicken! Are you scared?
あ、そうだよ。
Oh, right.
確かに堅実に行かんとね。
She has to play it safe.
このままいけば全然勝てるもんね。
If things go on like this, she'll win easily.
来いよ！
Bring it on!
それじゃあ、みこさんどうぞ。
Okay, Miko-san, go ahead.
いやー、フブさん、
Well, Fubuki,
待って。
Wait!
行くぞ！大丈夫？ポチ！
Here I go! Are you ready? Press!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
くそー！全部読まれちゃったよ！
Ugh! Damn it! You read me completely!
ちー！
Cheh!
なんとフブキ先輩27ポイントです。
Fubuki-senpai has a whopping 27 points!
イエーイ！
Yay!
やられたー！
I'm beat!
やっぱ取った後始末なのデカいポイント！おっしょ！
Those big points for the follow-up are huge! Let's go!
それではフブキ先輩、ミコ先輩が座るところ、当ててください。
Alright then, Fubuki-senpai. Guess where Miko-senpai will sit.
そうだな、でもまあ、ま、こっちかなと思いつつも、
Let's see. I think it might be over here, but...
ししゅした方がいい。これは堅実にししゅした方がいいので、ここにします。
I should defend it. I'll play it safe and defend this one. I'll pick here.
“ししゅ”じゃないですか？
Don't you mean 'shishu'?
ししゅ。
Shishu.
10、しゅしゅ、ししゅね、ししゅ。
10. 'Shushu.' No, 'shishu.'
しゅしゅ、ししゅね。
'Shushu.' 'Shishu,' right?
かわいい。
So cute.
後攻 さくらみこ
Attacker: Sakura Miko
なんだい？
What is it?
みこが10取りに来ようとしてるって思ってるんでしょう？
You think Miko is going to go for the 10, don't you?
思わねえよ。
I don't think that.
みこさんはだって賢いもん。
Miko is smart, you know.
え？
Huh?
みこさんは賢いからって思って設置した。
I set it up thinking that Miko-san is smart.
みこ賢いの？
Miko is smart?
賢いな。今まで電撃あびてないんだよ？
You are. You haven't been zapped so far.
まあ、確かに。それはそう。
Well, that's true. That's for sure.
8や！
It's 8!
お、いいのかい？
Oh, are you sure?
8！
8!
それでは、電撃をどうぞ。
Alright then, activate the electricity, please.
じゃあな、みこ。
See you later, Miko.
やだ！
No!
いやー！
Aah!
いやー、どっちかなとは思ってたけど。
Wow, I thought it might be one of them...
やったー！
Yay!
まあこれでししゅしたということでね。
Well, with that, you've defended it.
（笑）
(Laughter)
セーフ。でもいい勝負、いい勝負。めっちゃいい勝負してる。
Safe. But this is a good match. A very good match.
ではですね、ここから第4ラウンドということで、倍宣言を使うことができるようになります。
Okay, from here, it's Round 4, which means you can now use the Double Down.
倍宣言！
Double Down!
なるほど、倍宣言か。
I see, Double Down.
これね、成功すれば獲得ポイントがなんと2倍になるという代物です。
If you succeed, the points you get will be doubled.
倍宣言
Double Down
第4ラウンド以降に一度だけ使用可能。成功すれば獲得ポイントがx2。仕掛ける側は電撃装置を2個仕掛けるので、それ相応のリスクを伴います。
Can be used once from Round 4 onwards. If successful, earned points are doubled. However, the attacker must set two zappers, adding risk.
なるほど。うわ、2個きついな。
I see. Wow, setting two is tough.
さあ、どうするの？どうするの？
So, what will you do? What will you do?
どうしますか、フブキ先輩。倍宣言、使いますか？
What will you do, Fubuki-senpai? Will you use the Double Down?
倍宣言するのか、フブキ。どうすんのかな…いやでも倍だなあ。
Is Fubuki going to use Double Down? What should I do... But double points...
か…い…使います！
This... I... I'll use it!
お！倍宣言！
Oh! A Double Down!
行きましょう！さすがギャンブラー！
Let's go! I'm a gambler!
待って、倍宣言！
Wait, Double Down!
行きましょう！当んねえからよ！
Let's go! You won't hit me!
ではミコ先輩、今回は2カ所、電撃、設置してください。
Okay, Miko-senpai, please set two zappers this time.
いやー、どうしよっかなー。
Oh man, what should I do?
え、倍ってことは、えっと、座ったところの倍の点数もらえるってことすよね。
Wait, 'double' means she'll get double the points of where she sits, right?
そうです。
That's right.
なるほど。てことは、まずマストで10やな。
I see. In that case, 10 is a must.
10は1個入れるとして、こことこことこことこことここのどこに入れるかっちゅー話やな。
If I put one on 10, the question is where to put the other one...
なんやら10は絶対に仕掛けてる読みで
In fact, I'm reading that she definitely trapped 10,
10外して5、6に仕掛けても良いまである
so it might be a good idea to avoid 10 and trap 5 and 6.
確かに。うん。あり。それはあり。ありか。
That's true. Yeah. That's a possibility. That's right.
うん。
Yeah.
でもひよっちゃうよなあ
But she might chicken out.
うーん。
Hmm.
6、10やな。10と6。
It's 6 and 10. 10 and 6.
点数が高いやつを潰していく。
I'll go for the high-scoring ones.
いや。でもな。
No. But...
5と10にします。
I'll go with 5 and 10.
はい。では設置をお願いします。
Yes. Please go ahead and set the traps.
さあ、どこを選ぶんだい
Now, which one will you choose?
いやー
Man...
座る椅子をね、決めてください。
Please decide which chair to sit on.
2個ですからね。
There are two of them, right?
2個だよな。仕掛けられてるの。
There are two of them, right? The ones that are trapped.
ここはまずない。ここは絶対ない。
It's definitely not this one. Definitely not this one.
ここかここかここなんだ。はいはいはい。
It's either here, here, or here. Yes, yes, yes.
ここは絶対仕掛けられてる。倍で取られちゃうと困ると思うから。
This one is definitely trapped. She wouldn't want me to get double points.
絶対みこさんは防御する。じゃあ、5と6じゃどっちかって話なんだよね。
Miko will definitely be on the defensive. So, it's between 5 and 6.
どの番号が好き？
What number do you like?
いや、みこは3と5が好きだよ。3と5はね、確かにみこだもんね。
Miko likes 3 and 5. Right, 3 and 5, that's her name.
あー、そうかそうかそうか。
Oh, right, right, right.
でもなんか10と6はあからさますぎる気がするから、なんか1個飛ばして5に仕掛けてそうだから6にしようかな。
But 10 and 6 seem too obvious. Maybe she skipped one and chose 5. I'll go for 6.
読んでる。やっぱそうだ。完全に読んでる！
She's reading her. That's it. She's reading her perfectly!
完全に読まれてる。
She's being read perfectly.
完全に読んでる。
She's reading her perfectly.
怖いけど6、6、6だ！ああ、怖い！
It's scary, but 6...6...It's 6! Oh, it's scary!
はい。はい、歌が怖い。
Okay. Okay, the song is scary.
いや、絶対5と10。電撃は10...わかったわかった。
No, it's definitely 5 and 10. The shock on 10... Okay, okay.
行くぞ！
I'm going!
5か6か10か1か2か
Is it 5, 6, 10, 1, or 2?
絶対見ない。
I'm definitely not looking.
行きますよ！はい！3、2、1！おっしゃ！
Here we go! Okay! 3, 2, 1... Yes!
やったー！セーフ！
Yes! I'm safe!
うわあ！すごいなあ。
Wow! That's amazing.
え、だって5と10？
Wait, was it 5 and 10?
12点も取られちまったか。
She took 12 points from me.
ふうう！まじでこわすぎる！
Whew! That was so scary!
おー！え、でもあと1点じゃん！
Oh! But she's only one point away!
え、本当に？これ39点？
Wait, really? Is this 39 points?
計算間違えたー！
I miscalculated!
やばい。計算間違えてるw
Oh no. She miscalculated. (laughs)
なんで？計算間違えたってどういうことだよ！
What? What do you mean you miscalculated?!
倍、どうしますか？当たり前だろ、倍プッシュや！
Double? What will you do? Of course! I'm doubling down!
倍プッシュしかない。倍プッシュいただきました。
No choice but to double down. We have a double down.
それでは、フブキ先輩。2か所に仕掛けてください。
Alright then, Fubuki-senpai. Please set the traps in two locations.
はい。みこやな。これは、これはもうみこに仕掛けるしかない気がする。
Okay. 'Miko', huh. This time, I feel like I have no choice but to trap her.
あー、なるほど。そういう読み方するってこと？
Oh, I see. So that's how she's reading it?
2と1は絶対座らないもんね。座んないね。
She'd never sit on 2 or 1. She won't.
これでみこちが10、10座れたらすごいぞ。
It'd be amazing if Miko could sit on 10 now.
ちょっと痛いけど。かなり痛いけど。
It'll hurt a bit, though. A lot, actually.
いやでもこれ面白いね。
But hey, this is interesting.
あー面白いね。どう来るんだ、みこさん。
Yeah, it's interesting. What will you do, Miko-san?
どうも。いやー。
Hello. Oh man...
これかなりの終盤じゃない？フブさん。
Isn't this pretty much the endgame, Fubuki-san?
そうですね、もうね。
That's right, it is.
1や。
It's 1.
おお、早いですね。
Oh, that was fast.
次のターン、ふぶさんを当てる
Next turn, I'll get Fubuki-san.
それしかみこに勝ち目はない
That's Miko's only shot at winning.
ダッサいダッサい
How lame! Lame!
1/4の勝負。
A 1-in-4 gamble.
だってそうしかないもん。それしかない！
It's the only way! The only way!
1で、次絶対ふぶさんを負かす。
I'll get 1 point, and then I'll definitely beat Fubuki-san.
では、電撃をどうぞ。
Okay, go ahead and press the button.
いやー、いやー。
No, no...
みこさん。
Miko-san.
どこだ、どこだ、5、5か。
Where is it? Where? 5? Is it 5?
3と5だよ！
It's 3 and 5!
あ！みこね！みこビービー！
Ah! Miko-ne! Miko Bibi!
やったぜ！
I did it!
え！？10も残ってたの！？
Huh?! There was a 10 left too?!
そうだよ！
Yes, there was!
なんでだよ！
Why?!
せっかくのチャンスを。
You wasted such a good chance.
はあ、みこちゃんのチャンスだったのに。
Sigh... It was Miko's chance.
みこちゃん、じゃあ今1とって、2点だね。
Miko-chan, so you got 1, that's 2 points.
では、みこ先輩。
Alright Miko-senpai,
仕掛ける場所、今回は1箇所です。選んでください。
this time you can set it in one place. Please choose.
2取ればいいだけだもん、だって。
I just need to get 2 points, right?
ていうのを予想して、
Anticipating that...
だから、3ってなると思う。
so, I think she'll go for 3.
決めましたか？どうぞ。仕掛けてください。
Have you decided? Go ahead. Set the trap.
やった。
Done.
でも私的にフブさんは
But personally, I think Fubuki-san...
勝ち方にこだわりそう
would be particular about how she wins.
じゃあ2とかには座りたくないってこと？
So she wouldn't want to sit on 2?
10とかにいくんじゃない？
Won't she go for 10?
「10に仕掛けないだろう」とか言って。
Saying "She wouldn't set a trap on 10."
さあ、1/4ですよ、ふぶさん。
Well, it's a 1-in-4 chance for you.
1/4か。まあまあまあ、どうせこの辺に仕掛けてそう。
1-in-4, huh. Well... I have a feeling she set the trap somewhere around here.
そう、だってもう1ポイント取ればいいって絶対思ってるから
Right, she's definitely thinking she just needs one more point,
このちっちゃいところに仕掛けるけども
so she'll trap a small number...
10を取る！
but I'll pick 10!
え？
Huh?
お、ほら。
Oh, see?
え、エンタメ...エンタメやで？
For enter... for entertainment, you know?
エンタメなら1に座った人に言われたくないね。
Entertainment? I don't want to hear that from someone who sat on 1.
エンタメやで！
It's for entertainment!
エンタメは10。
Entertainment is 10.
あ、おしゃれ！はいその通り。
Oh, stylish! Exactly.
正論。論破。正論論破だ〜。
Sound argument. Refuted. I've been soundly refuted.
しかも倍プッシュしたのに〜。
And I even doubled down...
それでは電撃をどうぞ。
Well then, please press the button.
怖い！
I'm scared!
行くぞ！はい、はい！
Here I go! Yes, yes!
くっそー！
(Scream)
よっしゃー！
Alright!
すごーい！
Amazing!
ふぶき先輩が49点！
Fubuki-senpai gets 49 points!
なんだよ、もう！
What the heck?!
日和って1に座れてる場合じゃねえよな！
This is no time to chicken out and sit on 1!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
全部当てたよ？
You guessed it all?
全部みこの予想を当てたからね？
You guessed all of Miko's predictions, didn't you?
やってた。全部仕掛けてたよね。
She did. She had it all figured out.
全部あってた。
You were completely right.
怖いよ！すごすぎる。
That's scary! It's too amazing.
どちらも1回も当たりませんでしたね。
Neither of them got zapped once.
確かに。まだ莉々華しかくらってない。
That's true. Only Ririka has been zapped.
かわいそう莉々華。
Poor Ririka.
ということで、今回みこ先輩が負けてしまったんですが
And so, Miko-senpai lost this time, but...
みこ先輩、点数が26点ということで、莉々華が0点だったので...
her score was 26 points, while Ririka's was 0...
なんでだよ...
Why are you bringing that up...
なんと、予選の第3試合ですね
so in the 3rd qualifying match,
ミオ先輩と戦うのは、みこ先輩となりました！
Mio-senpai will be facing Miko-senpai!
いけ！頑張ってくれ、ミオ！
Go for it! Do your best, Mio!
予選リーグ第3試合は、大神ミオ対さくらみこ！
The 3rd qualifying league match is Ookami Mio vs. Sakura Miko!
はい、準備はいいですか？
Okay, are you ready?
えー、じゃあ
Uh, well...
吾が先行で。
I'll go first.
じゃ、先に座るってこと？
So, you'll sit first?
じゃあどうぞどうぞ
Go ahead, please.
え？わかりました。
Huh? Alright.
ということでMioはじゃあ一旦、下へ。はい、こちらの方で。
So Mio, for now, please step down. Yes, over here.
はい。
Yes.
ではみこさん
Okay, Miko-san.
座る椅子を予想してください
Please predict which chair she'll sit in.
いや、一番最初結構難しいけど
Man, the first one is pretty tough, but...
12とかね、取られたら嫌だけどね
Like 12, I'd hate it if she took it.
さっきそれで12に座られてな、負けたんだよな
Last time she sat in 12 and I lost, you know.
12.
では仕掛けてください
Okay, please set the trap.
12にしよ
I'll go with 12.
はい
Okay.
勝手なミオ先輩のイメージだと
Based on my own image of Mio-senpai,
結構無難な
she'd go for a pretty safe...
9とか… 8とか
like 9... or 8.
ねぇ、座りそうですよね！
Yeah, she seems like she would, right!
確かに来そうではある
Yeah, it does seem likely.
割と安全そうなところに
She'd go for a relatively safe place.
ついにうちの番が来てしまいましたか
Has my turn finally come?!
そうですよ
Yes, it has.
ま、うちは最初は7から行こうと思います
Well, I think I'll start with 7.
7から？(動揺)
From 7?! (Shaken)
はい
Okay.
なるほどね
I see.
あーやっぱり
Ah, as expected.
やっぱり
As expected.
いかないですよね、最初は
She wouldn't go for it at first, would she?
あえて外してくるということですか
So you're saying she's intentionally avoiding it.
そうです
That's right.
じゃあ行きますよ。はい。
Okay, here we go. Yes.
電気！
Bzzzt!
余裕ぶってる。余裕そうだ！
She's so calm. She looks so calm!
スタート！待て！
Start! Wait!
セーフ！
Safe!
まあまあまあまあ、一旦ね
Well, well, well, for the first one.
7はどうぞどうぞと
I'll let you have 7.
まあまあ、じゃあ7ポイントいただきということで
Well then, I'll take my 7 points.
では、ミオさん
Okay, Mio-san.
ミコさんが座る椅子を予想してください
Please predict which chair Miko-san will sit in.
そうですね
Let's see.
みこちは結構ビビりで
Miko-chi is quite a scaredy-cat,
おそらく今回は12に座らないんじゃないかなって思う
so I don't think she'll sit in 12 this time.
なので、そうだな、ちょっとあえて
So, let's see... I'll intentionally,
序盤ですし、さっき7に座れたので外していこうと思います
it's early, and I sat in 7, so I'll avoid it.
9！
9!
じゃ、仕掛けてください
Okay, please set the trap.
意外とみこ先輩は大きい数字に座らないなって思いました
Surprisingly, I didn't think Miko-senpai would sit on a high number.
今ね、すごいビビってるんですよね
She's really scared right now, you know.
ビビりに？
Of the shocks?
そう、はい。ビビっているっていう見解が
Yes. The assessment that she's scared
私とミオちゃんの間では出ました
is what Mio-chan and I came up with.
なるほどね
I see.
では、Mikoさん、座る椅子決めてください
Okay, Miko-san, please choose your chair.
えー
Ehh...
まあさっき7を取られてしまった
Well, she took 7 from me earlier.
ミオちゃんそっちのタイプねと
So Mio-chan is that type, huh...
まぁまんまと見破られていましたよ
Yep, she saw right through me.
なるほど
I see.
だからみこちゃんも
So Miko-chan will also,
ここらへんを取ると見せかけて
pretend to take one of these...
うわー！
Waaah!
12行くか！
I'll go for 12!
お！ああ！すごい！
Oh! Ahh! Amazing!
これ！まさかの！すごい！
This! No way! Amazing!
フブさんのところでは結構ひよっちゃったから
I got pretty scared during Fubuki's match, so...
では、押してください
Okay, please press the button.
12を取る！Mikoは12を取る！
I'll take 12! Miko will take 12!
12を取るなんてバカめ！
You fool for thinking I'd take 12!
セーーフ！
Saaafe!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
12人、12取れた！
Getting 12 when it's still available.
おー！いやこれは良いね！
Oh! Yeah, this is good!
これ策士策士。
She's a schemer, a schemer!
よし。どや顔。本当に良し…。
Alright. Such a smug look. Really alright...
やった！本当に良し。
I did it! Really alright.
交代戦です。
Time to switch.
チェンジです。
It's time to change.
10。はい、仕掛けてください。
10. Alright, please set your trap.
8に行きたいと思います。
I'd like to go for 8.
8？はい。
8? Yes.
堅実タイプか。
The steady type, huh?
セーフ！セーフセーフセーフセーフ！
Safe! Safe, safe, safe, safe!
なるほどね。なるほど。
I see. I see, I see.
あえての
I'll go with...
11で。
11.
じゃあ仕掛けてください。
Alright, set your trap.
この三択や。三択だ。
It's a three-way choice. Three-way choice.
あー！
Ah!
あ、やばい！
Oh no!
顔をそらしたけど。
She's looking away.
行けます！
I'm going for it!
いやー！
Ah!
うわー！やったー！
Whoa! Yay!
セーフ！
Safe!
では、ミオさん、座る椅子決めてください。
Alright, Mio-san, please choose your seat.
みこちが点数でかいところ2つ取っちゃってて
Miko took the two high-point seats.
ウチもでかいところ取らなきゃいけないってところじゃないですか。
So I have to get a high-point one as well, right?
局面的にはね。
In terms of the situation.
そうだね。
Right.
だからみこちの心理的には11か9に仕掛けた方がいいかなって
So psychologically, Miko should set a trap on 11 or 9.
でも、あの、11は攻めすぎなのかなと思うので9に行きたいと思います。
But... 11 is too aggressive, so I'll go with 9.
9？はい。
9? Yes.
じゃあ、お願いします。
Alright, go ahead.
行きますよ！
Here I go!
電撃食らえー！
Take this electric shock!
セーフ！やった！
Safe! Yay!
くそ！
Damn it!
セーフセーフ。9ポイント獲得です。
Safe, safe. You got 9 points.
うみこの予想。
The prediction was wrong.
ちょい乗りやがって。ドキドキドキ。
She got cocky. Thump, thump, thump.
いや、惜しかったな、みこさん。
Yeah, that was a close one for Miko.
いや、惜しかった。今二択だったもんな。
Yeah, it was a close one. It was a 50/50 chance.
9仕掛けたかったね。
I wanted to set a trap on 9.
わー、すごい。
Wow!
ここで11ポイント取っちゃえば、33ポイントになるんで
If she'd gotten 11 points here, she'd have 33 points.
あと7ポイントって考えると、4以上に座れれば勝てちゃう。
Then she'd just need 7 more points, so if she sat on 4 or higher, she'd win.
でもそこまで計算できないかもみこ先輩。
But Miko-senpai probably can't calculate that far.
うん、8×8,16って何。
Yeah. She was saying things like "8 times 8 is 16."
では、みこさん座る椅子選んでください。
Alright, Miko-san, please choose your seat.
でも、みこは点数を取っている。
But I'm winning on points.
ま、2ポイントですね、今。2ポイント。
A 2-point lead. I see.
2ポイント以上取れば一応
She's up by more than 2 points.
そして第4ラウンドから倍宣言が使用可能となりますので
And from the 4th round, you can use the Double-Down Declaration.
あ、確かに。
Oh, that's right!
そちらもね、ちょっと考慮して。
Please keep that in mind as well.
そう考えるとウチが11を倍にしたったら、もうじゃあもしあれだったら
In that case, if I had doubled down on 11, then I would've been able to...
うちが逆転勝利できるってことですね。
It means I can make a comeback.
ええ、確かに。11...
Oh, that's true. 11...
わ、わ、わ、わ…
Wah, wah, wah, wah...
みこがひよると思ってないでしょ。
You don't think I'll get scared, do you?
え？11に座ると思ってないでしょ？
Huh? You don't think I'll sit on 11, do you?
いやいやいや…いやいや、そんなことない、そんなことない。
No, no, no... No, no, of course not.
みこがひよってると思ってるなら…
If you think Miko is scared...
いや、そんなそんな。
No, no, no...
みこは11！
Miko is going for 11!
では、みこさん、お願いします。
Okay, Miko-san, please go ahead.
はい！
Yes!
みこっち、ごめん！
Mikocchi, I'm sorry!
いやーっ！
Aaaah!
（笑い声と叫び声）
*laughter and screaming*
ついに見られるんですね…。
So we finally get to see it...
ついに…。
Finally...
（笑い声）
*laughter*
来た！来た！
There it is! There it is!
やった！
Yes!
ようこそ〜！初めての電撃。
Welcome! To your first electric shock.
え、こん中に人いるだろ！
Hey, there's gotta be someone in there!
え、人だいな。
What? A person?
なんだ？（笑）
What was that? *laughter*
なんだ！なんだ！
What was that? What was that!
なんだ？やってません！おかしいだろ！
What was that? We didn't do anything! It's strange!
おかしいいただいて。
We've received your "strange"!
電気椅子！スイカみたいだ…。スイカみたい…。
The electric chair! It's like a watermelon... it's like a watermelon...
バン！めちゃくちゃ激しい！
Bang! It's so intense!
なんか、胴突きしてたぞ。
It was, like, pounding my torso.
（笑）
*laughter*
ということで。
And with that...
第4ラウンドに入りますので、ミオは倍宣言を使うことができます。
we're moving on to Round 4, so Mio can use the Double-Down Declaration.
おお！すごい！
Oh! Awesome!
すごいことなんで、別に今じゃなくても大丈夫ですけども。
It's a big deal, so you don't have to use it now, but...
次のラウンド、倍宣言使いますか？
Will you use the Double-Down Declaration in the next round?
じゃあ使います！わかりました！倍宣言です！倍！
Then I'll use it! Got it! It's a Double-Down Declaration! Double!
おい、なんでそんな楽しそうなんだよ！
Hey, why do you look so happy!?
なんか楽しそうだね。
You look like you're having fun.
なんでちょっとフフンとかやってんのよ！
Why are you going "hmph hmph" like that!?
では、みこさん、真ん中で決めましょう。
Okay, Miko-san, let's decide in the middle.
いやあ、これは…やらせたい…。
Man, this... I want to get her...
11は守らないと絶対にみこは逆転できないから。
If I don't guard 11, I absolutely can't make a comeback.
ミオファの「ファ」で4にしよう。
I'll go with "Fa" from "Miofa" and choose 4.
なんで「ファ」が4なんだろう？
Why is "Fa" 4?
え？フォーってこと？
Huh? You mean like "four"?
フォー？ミオファいないんですけど。
Four? There's no Miofa here though.
わかった。5と4。
I've got it. 5 and 4.
では、5と4にじゃ、仕掛けてください。
Alright then, please set the traps on 5 and 4.
おお、ええ…。11を空けてしまった。
Oh, wow... She left 11 open.
やった！これいいんじゃない？
Yes! Isn't this good?
いや…でも…まあ11座りづらいよな。
Well... but... It's hard to sit on 11.
座れる勇気よ、本当に。
It takes courage to sit there, really.
さすがにね、みこをバカだと思ってるから、
As expected, she thinks I'm an idiot,
11には来ないと思ってると思う。
so she probably thinks I won't go for 11.
11に星は賭けてると思うから、多分5か6なんだけども…。
I think she's betting on 11, so it's probably 5 or 6, but...
え、待って、11来たらさ…もう終わり。
Wait, if she comes to 11... it's over.
え？終わり？
Huh? It's over?
いやでも、あえて座らないと見せかけ…座るだろうと思って、
Well, but, she might pretend not to sit there... or think that she will sit there,
安牌だろうみたいな、そういう感じよな。
thinking it's a safe bet. Something like that.
では、ミオさん、倍宣言使用中ですので、仕掛けられてるのは2箇所と。
Alright, Mio-san, since you're using the Double-Down Declaration, traps are set in two places.
なっております。座る位置決めてください。
Please decide where you'll sit.
ふむふむ。
Hmm, hmm.
でもこれってウチが11選んで座れちゃったら
But if I choose 11 and sit on it,
これウチの勝ちですよね？
then that means I win, right?
そうです。
That's right.
仕掛けられていない限りはそうですね。
Unless it's been rigged, yes.
そうですよね。
That's right.
もう、そしたらウチはもうとりあえず11座ってみようかな。
Well then, I'll just go ahead and sit on 11.
よいしょっと。
Here I go.
本当にいいの？
Are you sure about this?
もう本当にいい、いいよ。もうだってさ
It's really fine. It's because...
まぁここでね、やっぱ大一番勝負していかないとね
Well, this is the big moment. I have to make my move.
分かんないんでねこればっかりは
You never know what will happen.
ええー！
Whoa!
勇気あるな〜！
She's so brave!
本当にすごいね！
That's really amazing!
あーあーあー
Ahhh...
押してください
Please press it.
うーん
Mmm.
両方
Both of them.
うー
Mmm.
だーっ！
Dah!
セーフ！ セーフ！
Safe! Safe!
ってことは？
Which means?
大神ミオの勝利！
Ookami Mio wins!
やったー！なんでそんな負けてくれるの？
Yay! Why did you let me win?
いー！なんでー！
Noo! Why?!
なんで11に仕掛けなかったの？
Why didn't you set the trap on 11?
最初はかけてた。
I did at first.
おー！
Oh!
11じゃん。マストだよね。
11 is the obvious choice.
うん。
Yeah.
11でまあ、ここらへんやなって。
I thought, 'It's got to be 11, somewhere around here.'
あ、逆に11だから外してくると思ったんだ！
Ah, so you thought I'd avoid 11 because it was too obvious!
甘いな。
You're naive.
いざという時に行く女です。
I'm the kind of woman who goes for it when it counts.
うーっ！
Ugh!
あー、そうですか。
Oh, is that so.
そっかー。
I see.
いや、度胸ありますねミオさん。
Wow, Mio-san has guts.
かっこよすぎる。
She's too cool.
なんでや！
Why?!
おー！
Oh!
何でみんなそんなみこのこと読んでくんだよ！
Why does everyone read me so well?!
誰か当てたい！
I want someone to guess right!
どんまいですね。
Too bad.
ではここから後半戦でーす！
Okay, let's start the second half!
誰か当ててる
Someone guessed right.
さあ、準決勝は星街すいせい対、大神ミオ！
Now, the semi-finals are Hoshimachi Suisei versus Ookami Mio!
ヤバい、気合の入り方が違うかもしれない。
Whoa, my level of enthusiasm might be different.
どっちがいい？
Which one do you want?
仕掛けたい。
I want to set the trap.
あ、じゃあウチが
Ah, then I'll...
はい。じゃあ、ミオさん先行でいきましょう。
Okay. Then, Mio-san, you go first.
ありがとうございます。じゃあ、行きます。
Thank you. Okay, here I go.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
よいしょ。
Alright.
では星街さん、ミオが座る椅子を予想してください。
Okay Hoshimachi-san, please predict which chair Mio will sit on.
え、さっき1回目ってどこ座りましたっけ？ミオさん。
Um, where did you sit the first time, Mio-san?
11？
11?
いや、7。7だ。
No, 7. It was 7.
7座ったんだ。
You sat on 7.
で、『同じようにいくと思ったか！』っていうことで
And then, she'd think, 'Did you think I'd do the same thing?'
10から上に座るんじゃないかなっていう予想はしています、今のところ。
So I'm guessing she'll sit on 10 or higher, for now.
まあ、ちょっと1回様子見はしときたいですね、11かな。
Well, I want to see what happens first... maybe 11.
ではミオさん、座る椅子を決めてください。
Okay Mio-san, please choose a chair to sit on.
えー、どうしようかなあ。
Hmm, what should I do?
精神統一みたいな感じで始めてるんですけど、大丈夫そうですかメンタル？
She's in a state of spiritual focus. Is her mental state okay?
（歌）Stellar Stellar～
(Singing) Stellar, stellar...
やばいそう… Stellar Stellar…
Oh no... Stellar, stellar...
えぇ、どうしよう…
Oh, what should I do...
まあ、ぶっちゃけ前半にはもう置いてないと思ってて
Well, to be honest, I don't think she placed it in the first half.
もう絶対に後半に置いているだろうなという予測は立つんですが
I'm guessing she definitely placed it in the latter half.
もうさっきからね、この辺の10から12っていうのは相当怪しいので
For a while now, the area from 10 to 12 has been very suspicious,
えー、9でいきたいと思います
so, uhm, I'd like to go with 9.
おっ！
Oh!
9か。9だ！
9, huh? It's 9!
すごい。まあ、でも賢いかもなー。うん
Amazing. Well, that might be a smart move. Yeah.
参ります
Here I go.
（電気が流れる音）
(Electricity zapping)
セーフ！怖い怖い怖い！怖いよー！うーん
SAFE! Scary, scary, scary! It's scary! Ugh...
連日は堅実さ
Day after day, steady as she goes.
さあ、9ポイントゲットです！
Alright, I got 9 points!
様子見、様子見。ドキドキするぜ。ピリつくなこりゃ
I'll see how it goes. My heart's pounding. This is getting tense.
へえ、衝動― なんなの？
Hey, impul— What is she doing?
ミオさん、すいちゃんが座る椅子を予想してください。－はい
Mio-san, please predict which chair Suichan will sit on. -Yes.
まあ、この範囲に仕掛けようかなとは思ってるんですけど、うーん
Well, I'm thinking of setting it in this range, but... umm...
10に仕掛けようと思います
I think I'll set it on 10.
ではどうぞ
Then, please proceed.
え、でもすいちゃん先輩意外と大きい数字座ってましたよね？
Wait, but didn't Suichan-senpai surprisingly sit on a high number?
座ってた！ねえ
She did! Right?
1に座るすいちゃん先輩見たくないもんな
I don't wanna see Suichan-senpai sitting on 1.
たしかに… おい、1に座ったぞみこ！
True... Hey, Miko, I'm the one who sat on 1!
後攻 星街すいせい
Second player, Hoshimachi Suisei.
星街さん。はい。座る椅子を決めてください
Hoshimachi-san. Yes. Please decide which chair to sit in.
ミオさん…－はい。－甘いです
Mio-san... -Yes. -You're naive.
え？私のことをナメないでください
Huh? Don't underestimate me.
もうバレてるってことですか？お願いします！
Does that mean you've already figured it out? Please!
やばい！土下座！
Oh no! She's prostrating!
土下座の星街！いや、どうしても電撃を喰らいたくない！
Prostrating Hoshimachi! I really don't want to get shocked!
何このキャラ？また土下座してる
What's with this character? She's prostrating again.
そこでもうプライド…ケツぐらい良いだろうがよ！
That's where her pride is... A butt's just a butt, who cares!
うちは11に仕掛けました
I... set it on 11.
あ、でも10かもしんない
Oh, but it might be 10.
11に…
On 11...
迷ってる。11か10に仕掛けたんですね？ーはい
She's hesitating. So you set it on 11 or 10, right? -Yes.
じゃああなたは12です
Then you're going for 12.
え？そんな…
Huh? No way...
じゃああなたは12に仕掛けたんです
Then you set it on 12.
嘘ついてるってことですか、ウチが？
Are you saying that I'm lying?
いや、やっぱり本当に11に仕掛けたんです。どっちなんだ？
No, you really did set it on 11. Which is it?
どっちですか！？
Which is it?!
こっちが聞きたいんすよ！
I'm the one who wants to ask!
混乱してる、大混乱だ。こんなすいちゃん見たことない、あんまり
She's confused, totally confused. I've never really seen her like this.
なんかさ、みこちと戦ってるときとさ、緊張感が違うの
When she's fighting against us, the tension is different.
ちょっと腹立つよね
It's a little irritating, isn't it?
たしかに…言われてみれば…ナメてる
True... Now that you mention it... She's looking down on us.
ナメられてますね。うん
We're being looked down on. Yeah.
その後もすいせいは悩み続け…さあ、12に。お！
After that, Suisei continued to worry... Okay, on 12. Oh!
（笑い声）ちょちょちょちょ
(Laughs) Wait, wait, wait, wait.
11に。あー。10に。あー
On 11. Ah... On 10. Ah...
8に
On 8...
ちょっと、ちょっと決めましょう。ちょっと、ちょっと決めましょう。ちょっと決めてですよね
Wait, wait, let's decide. Wait, we have to decide, right?
（歩き回る）まあ7ではないですよね、さすがに
(Walks around) Well, it's not 7, right? Of course not.
うーん、まあまあまあ…
Umm, well, well, well...
いや、なーし！
Yeah, no way!
うちってそんなに読みにくい？
Am I that hard to read?
9か10、あ、でも10かもしんない。
9 or 10... Ah, but it might be 10.
やばい。こんなに迷われるとは。
Oh, man. To think you'd be this torn.
じゃあ、行きます。
Okay, I'm going.
めっちゃ、めっちゃ悩んでる。
She's hesitating so much.
こんなことあんまないからね。
This doesn't usually happen.
はい、座ったらもう変更することはできません。
Once you sit, you can no longer change your choice.
では、ミオさん、お願いします。
Now then, Mio-san, please proceed.
うちを信じろ！
Believe in me!
てや！
Here I go!
はっ！
Huh?
違いましたね。
You were wrong!
セーフ！
Safe!
ということで星街さん、11ポイント獲得です！
So, Hoshimachi-san gets 11 points.
やー！
Nooo!
11でした。
It was 11.
危ない、危ない。
That was close.
危ない、危ない、危ない。
Close, close, close.
そんなに、そんなにうち読みにくいかな？
Am I really that hard to read?
余裕、余裕。余裕ですよ、全て。
It was easy. That was all an act.
ええ、やりましょうか。
Yeah, shall I do it?
では、星街さん、ミオの座る椅子を予想してください。
Alright, Hoshimachi-san, please predict Mio's chair.
ブチ当てたいですよ、正直。
I really wanna get it right, to be honest.
ま、ここは素直に。素直に私はいきたいと思います。
I'll be straightforward. I'll be straightforward with my choice.
素直に迷うやん。
You're hesitating even though you're being straightforward.
素直に迷ってんじゃん。
You're still hesitating.
早くしろよ！
Hurry up!
うん、その可能性ありますよ。
You seem to be taking me lightly.
「うん」が早いんだわ。
Your 'uh-huh' was too quick.
取られたらまずいと思うのは多分12、10、まあ、8もかなって感じで
The ones that would be bad to lose are probably 12, 10, well, and maybe 8.
ここまでは思考読み通りです。
So far, my thought process is right on track.
お！やばい、読まれているらしい。
Whoa! It seems she's being read.
なので、うちがここでもしかして、このあたりを取ってくるんじゃないかと読んで、実は10はなにもない。
So, since she might go for one of those, I'm predicting that 10 is actually empty.
お！
Oh!
だはっ
Huh?
はい、決まりました。では、星街さんお願いします。
Alright, I've decided. Now, Hoshimachi-san, please proceed.
いいんですね、ミオさん。
Are you sure, Mio-san?
はい！
Yes!
行きます。
I'm going.
はい！
Yes!
セーフ！
Safe!
セーフ。ミオ10ポイント獲得。やった！10ポイント！
Safe. Mio gets 10 points. I got 10 points!
因果律…
Causality...
これが…
This is...
大神ミオのやり方っちゅうわけや。
...this is Ookami Mio's way of doing things.
いやいやいやいや、そんな大したもんじゃないです。これで19ポイントとなりました。
No, no, no, no. It's not that big of a deal. So now it's 19 points.
はい。
Yes.
いやぁ、19ポイントはでかいぞ。
Wow, 19 points is huge.
ほぼ半分ですもんね？40ポイントまで。
That's almost halfway to 40 points, right?
では、ミオさん、ホシマチが座る椅子を予想してください。
Alright, Mio-san. Predict which chair Hoshimachi will sit on.
ウチとしては12点とか8点とかを取られるとちょっと痛いみたいな感じではあるんで。
If she takes 12 or 8 points, it would sting a little.
ここはあえての…
I'll take a chance and...
8にしようと思います。
I'm going with 8.
じゃ、仕掛けてください。
Okay, please set it up.
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Yoisho, yoisho.
12を除いて一番大きい数字だから、座るの怖い気がしますけどね？
Excluding 12, it's the biggest number, so I'd be scared to sit there, you know?
怖いなぁ。
Scary.
もう3回なら慣れたんじゃない？
She's been zapped 3 times, shouldn't she be used to it?
ちなみに4回ですけどね？
Actually, it's four times, isn't it?
最初のチュートリアル込みで。一人だけ4回食らってますけどね？
Including the first tutorial. She's the only one who's been zapped four times, right?
後攻 星街すいせい。
Next up, Hoshimachi Suisei.
ではホシマチさん、座る椅子を決めてください。
Alright Hoshimachi-san, please pick a chair to sit on.
ミオさん。
Mio-san.
はい。
Yes.
どこに仕掛けました？
Where did you set it?
ウチ爆弾魔か何かなのかな？
Am I some kind of bomberman or what?
追い詰められた爆弾魔。
The hunted bomberman.
まあ間違ってないです。どこに仕掛けたんですか？
Well, you're not wrong. Where did you set it?
うーん、ウチは12とかは取られちゃうとまずいかなと思って仕掛けたよ。
Umm... As for me... I set it thinking it would be bad if you took something like 12.
分かりました。
I get it.
信じてるのか信じてないのか若干わかんない。
I can't quite tell if she believes me or not.
これあの謎解くヒントになりますか？
Will this be a hint for solving the puzzle?
うーん、どうですかね。
Hmm, I wonder.
じっくりと考えて。
She's thinking it over carefully.
顔が…
Her face...
四股踏んでんの？
Are you doing a sumo stomp?
はい。
Yes.
座った！
She sat down!
やった！
Yes!
来た来た来た来た来た来た！
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here!
座りましたらもう変更はできません。
Once you've sat, you cannot change your choice.
ミオさん、ここなんですか？
Mio-san, is it this one?
そんなのわかんないですよ、ウチにも。
I wouldn't know.
うちは爆弾魔じゃないもん。ミオさん。
I'm not a bomberman! Mio-san.
はい。
Yes.
お願いします。
Please.
はい。
Okay.
すいちゃん、うちは12番に仕掛けたんだってば！
Sui-chan! I told you I set it on number 12!
（歌）知らんから
(Sings) I wonder if you knew...
星街！
Hoshimachi!
星街！すいちゃん！すいちゃん！
Hoshimachi! Sui-chan! Sui-chan!
ここで『Stellar Stellar』
And here comes "Stellar Stellar."
ここでステラステラ。
Here's "Stellar Stellar."
やったー！
Yes!
すごい、姫森！
Amazing, Himemori!
やったー！
Yes!
こっちの世界へようこそ。
Welcome to this side of the world.
ふにゃん。
Hmph!
悔しみの表情。
What a bitter expression.
やめてこれ表情は…
Don't stop, the expression...
正解いたしました。
You've guessed correctly.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
すいちゃんの11ポイントがなくなります。
Sui-chan's 11 points will be gone.
わああ！
Whaaa!
ではホシマチさん、ミオが座る椅子を予想してください。
Well, Hoshimachi-san, guess which chair Mio will sit on.
7か12だと思うんすよ。
I think it's 7 or 12.
今まで自分の思考が外れまくってるんで、
But since my guesses have been so wrong...
もう8。
I'll go with 8.
自分を。
Myself...
自分を信じない。
Don't trust myself.
そういうこと。
That's how it is.
自分を信じない？
Don't trust myself?
そうだ。
That's right.
一番最初に当たった相手がクソ雑魚すぎただけだぞ。
My first opponent was just too weak.
わかった？
Got it?
ふぶちゃん。
Fubuki-chan.
いいね。
Right.
ケツを守っていきたい私は。
I want to protect my butt.
よろしく。
Here we go.
決めていただいてｗ
Go ahead and decide.
8。
Eight.
いや、仕掛けてください。
No, you make the first move.
8なの。
Is it eight?
8…めっちゃ迷う…8なの？マジで？
Eight... I'm so confused... It's eight? For real?
この真剣さを俺たちにくれよって感じだけどね。
I wish they'd show us this level of seriousness.
おかしい。
Weird.
なんか、ズル。
It's like... cheating.
ズルではないかｗ
Isn't that cheating?
先攻 大神ミオ。
First up: Ookami Mio.
ではミオさん、座る席決めてください。
Alright Mio-san, please decide which seat to take.
決めてきました？
Have you decided?
あっ、まだ決めてないです。
Oh, I haven't decided yet.
まだ決めてないです。
Not yet.
ふむー。
Hmm...
ここは倍の追い上げ潰しの12いっときますか。
To crush her comeback, should I go for the double-up 12?
こっち見ないで！こっち見ないでください！
Don't look at me! Please don't look at me!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
顔に出ちゃった。
It showed on my face.
顔に出てるなぁ。
It's all over your face.
もう負け宣言ですね、これは。
This is basically a declaration of defeat.
こっち見ないでください。あ、そっち見ちゃいけないんだ。
Please don't look at me. I'm not supposed to look that way.
もう決まりましたね。決まりましたね。座る席決まりましたね。
You've decided. You've decided. You know which seat. Okay.
では星街さん、お願いします。
Alright, Hoshimachi-san, please.
あなたの電撃を食らった姿が見たい。
I want to see you get electrocuted.
セーフ！
SAFE!
やったー！
Yes!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
ということでミオさん、12ポイント獲得です。
And with that, Mio-san gets 12 points!
やばい。
Oh no.
あとで殴られるかもしれない。
I might get hit later.
（笑）
(laughs)
よっしゃー！
Alright!
ではミオさん、すいちゃんが座る席を予想してください。
Okay, Mio-san, please predict where Sui-chan will sit.
うーん、なんかちょっと良い感じにとんとん拍子で来すぎてるからなぁ。
Well, things have been going a little too smoothly for her.
すいちゃん的にはここで高い点数をいきたいのか、それとも…うーん。
Is Sui-chan going for a high score, or... hmm...
後攻、星街すいせい。では星街さん、座る席を選んでください。
Next up, Hoshimachi Suisei. Hoshimachi-san, pick a seat.
思考を教えてください。
Tell me your thoughts.
どういう思考でした、今。心理戦なんで。
What was your thinking just now? It's a mind game.
どういう思考を…？
What thoughts...?
うちの思考ってことですか？
You mean my thoughts?
どういう思考ですか、はい。
Yes, what was your reasoning?
まあ、うちの思考的には、次から倍宣言が使えるので、
Well, my thinking was, since we can use the double-up
（すいちゃんは）逆に高い点数は取っておいた方が良いと思った。
I thought it would be better to get a high score instead.
あ、私が。そう。
Oh, for me? Right.
って考えるんじゃないかと考えました。
That's how I thought she would think.
そう考えてました。
That's what I was thinking.
素直ですね。そうですよね。
You're so straightforward.
私…でも今日決めてきて、もう自分の心に従いたい。
But I... I decided today that I want to follow my heart.
いいよね。もういいよ、それで。
Right? That's fine, go for it.
従いたいので。
I want to follow it, so...
自分の心に従おう。
Follow your heart.
なんかさっきは何かが間違えちゃったんだろうね。
I guess something went wrong before.
絶対に8に仕掛けられてるって今思ってるんですけど、
I'm sure there's a trap at eight right now.
8に仕掛けられてると思ってる？
You think there's a trap at eight?
仕掛けられてると思ってるんですけど、でも私は…決めてきたんで、もう。
I do, but... I've made up my mind, so...
何回でも電撃をくらいたい
I'm ready to take as many electric shocks as it takes.
くらいたい？もうそれはちょっとおかしくなっちゃってるよ
You want to? I think you're starting to sound a little weird.
大丈夫かな？電撃くらいすぎておかしくなっちゃってるかも
Are you okay? Maybe you've taken too many shocks.
決めてきたんで
I've made up my mind.
うん
Yes.
決めてきたんで
I've made up my mind.
まあじゃあお好きなようにしていただいて
Well then, please choose whichever you like.
決めてきたんで
I've made up my mind.
勇気が出ないです
I can't work up the courage.
ミオさん勇気をください
Mio-san, give me courage.
早く座れ！
Just sit down already!
すいちゃんならできる、大丈夫だよ
You can do it, Suichan. It's okay.
本当ですか
Really?
うん。ありがとうございます。大丈夫、いけるいける
Yes. Thank you. You can do it.
ありがとうございます。耐えられるよ
I'll be okay. You can take it.
ごめんなさいミオさん
I'm sorry, Mio-san.
でもどうしてもやっぱ怖くて…
But I'm just too scared...
早くやれッ！
Hurry up and do it!
怖いよね
It's scary, isn't it?
うん…すいません。そっちに行きましたか
Yeah... sorry. I'll go with that one.
はい
Yes.
というわけででは、ミオさん、お願いします
Alright then. Mio-san, if you please.
自分の心に素直になろう！
Be true to your heart!
セーフ！
Safe!
何番？
Which one was it?
6番です。危なかったね
Number 6. That was close.
危なかった。セーフ！
I'm safe. Oh, safe.
危ない危ない！セーフ！危なかったー！うー！
That was close! So close! Oh my god.
危なかった危なかった、ほんと危なかった。惜しかったな。惜しかったですね。
That was so close, seriously. That was a close one.
はい。ということで、続いてなんですけどミオさん！
Okay, so next up is... Mio-san!
はい！続いてから4ラウンド目に入りますけども、倍宣言使われますか？
Yes! Moving on to the fourth round. Will you use your double-down?
お！えっと、なるべく多く残っている時に倍宣言を使った方がいいと
Oh! I think it's best to use the double-down when there are more chairs left.
思いますので、倍宣言、使いたいと思います
So I'd like to use it.
わかりました。では仕掛ける箇所が2つになりますので、よろしくお願いします
Got it. So there will be two trap chairs. Good luck.
頑張るぞー！
I'll do my best!
2つ予想してください
Please predict two spots.
2か所ですよね。普通に考えたら8と7っすよね
Two spots, right? Logically, it's 8 and 7.
6取られても負けなんで、4取ったら8ポイントになって39になるわけじゃないですか
Even if 6 is taken, it's not a loss. If she takes 4, it's 8 points, making it 39.
ミオさんはでも攻めると思います。8、7、6、このどこか絶対座ります
But I think Mio-san will be aggressive. 8, 7, 6... she'll definitely sit somewhere there.
8と7です
8 and 7.
ちょっと安牌の4
I'll play it a bit safe with 4.
うん。ああ、怖い！セーフ！
Hmm. Ah, so scary! Safe!
4に座ったので、倍になりまして8ポイント獲得。これにより39ポイント
Since she sat on 4, the points are doubled to 8, bringing her to 39 points.
倍宣言します！
I'll use my double-down!
おー！倍宣言！分かりました。まぁそりゃそうだよね
Ooh! A double-down! Got it. Well, of course.
仕掛ける箇所は2か所です
There will be two traps.
はい。では後攻星街すいせい
Yes. Alright then. It's Hoshimachi Suisei's turn.
さん座る席を選んでください。どうぞ
Please choose your seat.
2か所仕掛けられております
There are two traps set.
まさか1にはいかないですよね？
Surely you won't go for 1, right?
ちょっと思いました
I was thinking about it.
思いました？
You were?
思いました。まさかまさかまさか。危ない危ない
I thought so... No way... no way...
まさか。1、2はないです
It can't be 1 or 2.
え？
What?
バカにしてる？
Are you making fun of me?
バカにしてる？バカにされてますよ
Are you making fun of me? You're being made fun of.
でもみこ的には、このときは1に座ったけど、8選んでもさ、16ですもんね
But for Miko, this time I sat on 1, but even choosing 8 would be 16 points.
そうなんだ。どの数字を取られても関係ないから
That's right. No matter what number she gets,
もうミオ先輩を0点にすることを考えた方が、そう、そういうことよ
it's better to just focus on getting Mio-senpai to zero points. That's it.
まぁそれで負けたんですけど
Well, I lost doing that though...
6 とかどうすか？
How about 6?
あー、まあ、でもそこの3つちょっと怪しいなって思いますよね。
Ah, well, those three seem a bit suspicious, don't they?
7は？
What about 7?
あ、怪しいですよ、そこの3つは。
Oh, they're suspicious. Those three are.
8は？
What about 8?
もうもちろん怪しい怪しい怪しい。
Of course, it's suspicious, suspicious, suspicious.
すごい悩んでる。
She's really struggling with her decision.
一度座ったら変えてはいけない
Once you sit down, you cannot change.
一度座った席は移動は...
Once you've sat on a seat, moving is...
自分を信じよう。
Trust yourself.
そうですよ、自分を信じなきゃ。
That's right, you have to trust yourself.
自分を信じよう。
Trust yourself.
オッケー。
Okay.
もう何も怖くない。皆さん、お願いします。
I'm not afraid anymore. Let's do this.
もう何も怖くない。
You're not afraid of anything anymore.
そうだよね。自分を信じなきゃだよね。
That's right. You have to believe in yourself.
えい！
Go!
（絶叫）
(Screams)
あー、アウト！
Ah, she's out!
やりましたね。
She did it.
（笑い）
(Laughter)
アウト！
Out!
やった！
Yes!
バカめ！
You fool!
（笑い）
(Laughter)
どうですか星街さん？
How do you feel, Hoshimachi-san?
痛くねえし。
It doesn't hurt.
（笑い）
(Laughs)
痛かったよね？
It hurt, right?
痛い…（泣）
It hurts... (crying)
痛かったよね？
It hurt, didn't it?
ごめんね？ 痛かったよね。
Sorry, okay? It hurt, right?
では星街さん、ミオが座る椅子を予想してください。
Alright Hoshimachi-san, please predict which chair Mio will sit on.
ミオさんあなたは強かった
Mio-san, you were strong.
あなたの表情からは何も見えなかったよ
I couldn't read your expression at all.
そう、無。あったのは無
Right, nothing. All there was was nothing.
虚無
Void.
虚無ミオめ…！
You nihilistic Mio...!
これぶち当てないといけないけど、案外、勝ち方にこだわってくるんじゃない？
I have to get this right, but aren't you fussy about how you win?
“大きな数字で終わりたい”そういう欲がミオさんの中に生まれてくる
'I want to end with a big number.' That desire will arise in you.
そうなったとき つまり選ぶのは 8
In that case, it means you'll choose 8.
ミオさんは8に座る。
Mio-san will sit on 8.
では、仕掛けてください。
Well then, please set the trap.
私には見えてる。
I can see it.
（笑い）
(Laughter)
見えてる。見えた。もう私は何も言わない。
I can see it. I saw it. I won't say anything more.
何も考えない。
I won't think about anything.
そう。あなたは8。あなたは8に座るの。
Yes. You're going to pick 8. You're going to sit on 8.
はい。
Yes.
いやーどうなるんだろう？でも逆に、1ポイントでも取ればっていう状況のときにあえて8とかに座らなそうだから
Hmm, what will happen? But, when you only need one point, you probably wouldn't sit on 8.
逆に8に仕掛けないと踏んで...
So she'll assume you won't set a trap on 8...
難しいよ。6個か。
This is hard. Six chairs left.
先攻 大神ミオ。座る席を選んでください。
First turn: Ookami Mio. Please choose your seat.
はい。
Yes.
うわー。
Whoa.
ま、うちは1点でも取れば終了なので、ここの心理をどう読んでくるかっていうのが問題だと思うんですけど。
Well, if I get even one point, it's over, so the problem is how she'll read my psychology.
ちょっと…はい。助言はいただきました
Well... yes. I have received some advice.
助言はいただいた？
You received advice?
なるほど
I see.
え、白上さんからってことですか？
You mean, from Shirakami-san?
フッ まさか…
Heh, no way...
神ですよ神
It was God. God.
ええ！？ 神？
What?! God?
神か。誰のことなんだろう？
God, huh? I wonder who that is.
まぁ、まあいいか
Well, whatever.
今使い所じゃないもんね神は多分。もうちょっと前に使っとくべきだったもんね
I shouldn't use the God card now. I should have used it earlier.
えへへへ
*laughter*
すごい…
Amazing...
刺してる刺してる
She's poking at her, poking at her.
畜生ミオ出てる！
Beastly Mio is showing!
なんか、最大の得点の8を選びそうだなと思うと思うんですけど
I think you think I'm going to pick 8, the highest number.
すべて仕掛けられてますよ、すべて
It's all a setup. All of it.
もしくは神の力使ったのかな？
Or maybe she used God's power?
えーと、最大得点か、まあ、もしくは1を選ぶじゃないかっていう予想
Either the highest score, or you think I'll pick 1...
から、真ん中を入れてるんじゃないか、真ん中に入れてるんじゃないかと思うので、あえてここは1、ぴったりでいきたいと思います！
...so I think you put a trap in the middle. I'll defy that and pick 1 for a perfect score!
では、星街さん。はい。お願いします
Well then, Hoshimachi-san. Yes. Please.
神の言うことは本当だった…
What God said was true...
あなたは8…あなたは8に座るの
You... are 8. You will sit on 8.
ちなみに神的には1かなって思いました
By the way, as God, I thought it'd be 1.
えっ！？もう変えられないですよ？
What?! You can't change it now, you know?
MC的には、なんか1かなって思いましたね。フフッ。もう変えられないですけどね
As the MC, I thought it would be 1. Heh heh. But you can't change it now.
セーフ！
Safe!
神の言うことは…お…大神ミオ勝利！
What God said... It's over... Okami Mio wins!
神の言うことは本当だった…
What God said... was true...
くっ！
Aaargh!
すいちゃん！
Sui-chan!
これが…(ペロッ) 敗北の味
This is... (Lick) The taste of defeat.
これが敗北の味
This is the taste of defeat.
敗北してる
She's defeated.
ということで、ぴったり40点でした！
And with that, it's a perfect 40 points!
はい、やったー！
Yes, I did it!
すごーい！
Amazing!
ピッタリ賞だ！ピッタリ賞だしフブキ先輩は読んでたし！
It's the perfect prize! And Fubuki-senpai read it!
決勝は、ミオ先輩VSフブキ先輩です！
The final match is Mio-senpai versus Fubuki-senpai!
フブさん…負けてくれ頼む
Fubuki-san... Please lose, I'm begging you.
この畜生をボコボコにしてくれ
Beat this beast to a pulp.
フブさんブチ当たれ/ミオさんブチ当たれ
Fubuki-san, hit the trap!/Mio-san, hit the trap!
意気込み聞いていきたいと思いますんですが、じゃまずミオ先輩からお願いします
I'd like to hear your thoughts. Let's start with Mio-senpai.
はい。うーん、なんか…勝っちゃいました〜！
Yes. Hmm, somehow... I just won~!
ふざけんじゃねえ！電撃食らえ！食らえ！
Don't mess with me! Eat this electric shock! Eat it!
コイツー…！
This bitch...!
いや〜おもろいな〜
Man, this is funny.
いや〜すいちゃん、普通にナチュラル煽りずっとされてたからね？
Man, Sui-chan was being naturally taunted the whole time, you know?
そうですね。畜生ミオですよこれ。畜生です。完全に畜生ですよ
That's right. That's beastly Mio. She's a beast. A complete beast.
えー、フブキにね、やっぱり企画者という事で、一回でも電撃食らわせて帰りたいと思ってます。よろしくお願いします！
As the planner, I want to make Fubuki feel the shock at least once before I go home. Let's do this!
はい、ありがとうございます。
Yes, thank you very much.
じゃ、次フブキ先輩もどうぞ。
Okay, Fubuki-senpai, your turn.
いやさっき、控室で星街に
Well, earlier in the waiting room, Hoshimachi...
ミオさんにブチ当ててくれって言われたので
told me, "Go get Mio-san for me."
頭を下げてお願いしました。
I bowed my head and begged.
「頼むッ…！」
Please!
頼むん！
「ミオさんを…頼むッ…！」
Mio-san... Please!
ちょっと星街の思いを胸に頑張っていきたいと思います。
I'll do my best with Hoshimachi's feelings in my heart.
なるほど。
I see.
頑張ってください。
Please do your best.
それではね、早速先攻後攻決めていただきたいと思うんですが
Alright then, I'd like you to decide who goes first.
どっちがいい？ミオ
Which do you prefer, Mio?
え、ほんとにどっちでもいい。
Uh, I really don't mind either way.
このゲームどっちでもいい。先に選んでいいよ。
This game, either is fine. You can choose first.
あーじゃあ、じゃあ先攻もらっちゃおうかなじゃあ。
Oh, well then, I guess I'll take the first turn.
あ、じゃあうちが仕掛ける側ってことね。
Oh, so I'll be the one setting the trap.
そうそうそうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
はい、ではフブキ先輩が先攻、ミオ先輩が後攻ということで
Okay, so Fubuki-senpai will go first, and Mio-senpai will go second.
行くぞー、行くぞー。
Let's go, let's go.
お願いします。
Let's begin.
はーい。
Okay.
じゃあ楽しみにしてるぜ、ミオ。
I'm looking forward to it, Mio.
痛さ2倍にしてくんねぇかな決勝。
I wonder if they could double the pain for the finals.
たしかに。
That's right.
それでは、フブキ先輩、どの椅子に座るか決めてください。
Alright, Fubuki-senpai, please decide which chair to sit on.
ええー！
Ehhh!
考えない。何も考えないけど、直帰とこうか。どこに仕掛けたんだい？
I won't overthink it. Just my gut. Where'd you set it, huh?
ええー。
Ehhh.
どこに仕掛けたんでミオは。
Where did you set it, Mio?
えっとー
Umm...
うちぃは、えっとでもフブキは欲張りキツネだから、高い点数のところに仕掛けた方がいいかなとは思った。
Well, Fubuki is a greedy fox, so I thought it'd be best to set it on a high-point number.
これよ、このポーズ。
This is it, this pose.
ミオのこのポーズ。
Mio's pose.
ミオのw
Mio's, lol.
ミオのこのポーズ！
Mio's pose!
なにお前w
What are you doing? lol
どうした？ミオちゃんに対して。
What's with you? Towards Mio-chan.
このポーズだよ。
This pose.
ちいかわやん。
That's Chiikawa.
畜生…！！
Dammit...!!
ミオは畜生なんだ。
Mio is a beast.
なるほど。まあこの辺だよね。別にこの辺だよね。
I see. Well, it's around here. It must be around here.
この辺だけど、でもミオは意外とずらしてくるから、12は行けるはず。
It's around here, but Mio is surprisingly tricky, so 12 should be safe.
お！
Oh!
決断が早い！
Such a fast decision!
それでは、電撃、どうぞ！
Alright, electric shock, go!
え、そうなのかなあ、果たして
Huh, I wonder if that's right...
はい！
Here!
おお！セーフ！
Oh! Safe!
すごーい！
Amazing!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
星街いけるぞこれ。
Hoshimachi, I can do this!
12取ってる！
She got 12!
すごい。じゃあ12ポイント。
Amazing. So, 12 points.
どこだった？
Where was it?
え、えっとね、10です。
Uh, umm, it was 10.
10かよ！
It was 10?!
やっぱこの辺なんだ。
So it was around here.
うわーよかった、こえー。
Phew, that was close. Scary.
人間のフリしてますね。
She's pretending to be human.
人間のフリしてる。そうです。
Pretending to be human. That's right.
フブさんね。
Fubu-san.
人間のフリするんですよ。
She pretends to be human.
どういうこと…w
What do you mean... lol
いやこれめっちゃおもろいな、本当に。
Man, this is really funny.
しかもケツ電気が痛くて
And the butt shock hurts...
やっぱり緊張感がある。「もうやりたくない」っていう。
so there's tension. That "I don't wanna do this again" feeling.
そうね。
Right.
やっぱ生ぬるいね、我々いつも。
We're too soft, usually.
「本当に当たりたくない」っていう気持ちがあるからこそのこの面白さよ。
The fun comes from that feeling of "I really don't want to get hit."
そうでしょ？みこさん。
Right? Miko-san.
うん、本当に当たりたくなかった。
Yeah, I really didn't want to get hit.
それでは、どの椅子に座るか選んでください。
Alright, please choose which chair to sit in.
選べミオ。
Choose, Mio.
選べミオ！
Choose, Mio!
いや、12取られちゃったからな。
Aww, she took 12.
そうだぞ。12を取った。
That's right. I took 12.
でもね、多分ね、12を取ったということは、もう上の方はちょっと取られたくないなっていう気持ちだと思う。
But, you know, since she took 12, I think she feels like she doesn't want the other high numbers taken.
そりゃそうだよ。
Of course.
そりゃそうじゃ！
Of course it is!
やめてほしいなそうじゃん、やめてほしいよな
I wish you wouldn't, really. I wish you'd stop.
それはそう。やめてほしい。
That's right. I wish you'd stop.
でも、あの、まぁフブキに当てればいいっていう話なので
But, well, the point is to just hit Fubuki, so...
やめろ！ウチがくらわない方が大事
Stop it! It's more important that I don't get zapped.
くらわずに得点を重ねた方がいいかなって思うので
I think it's better to rack up points without getting zapped, so...
ちょっとあえて半端なところ、8いきたいと思います。
I'll dare to go for a random spot. I'll pick number 8.
はい
Alright.
行きます。
Here I go.
はい。くそ…ミオ！
Okay. Damn it, Mio!
それでは、電撃をどうぞ。
Alright, send the shock.
なんでなんなミオ。
Why are you like this, Mio?
キタァーーツ！！
HERE IT IS!
この野郎畜生ミオ…！
You damn beast, Mio!
当たりやがったな。
She actually hit it!
よっしゃ！すごい悲鳴
Alright! What a scream.
これが見たかった。
This is what I wanted to see.
三途の川渡ってこい！
Go cross the Sanzu River!
渡ってる。
She's crossing it.
大丈夫ですか？大丈夫？
Are you okay? Are you?
今、大変なことになってる。
Something terrible is happening right now.
お尻が４つに割れてるかもしれない。
Her butt might have split into four.
太ももにきた太もも…！
It hit my thigh, my thigh...!
生足だからか？
Is it because my legs are bare?
よだれ出た。
I drooled.
あ、いてぇ。やばいよお…
Ow, it hurts. This is bad...
泣いてる、泣いちゃった。
She's crying. She started crying.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございましたじゃないんだよ！w
It's not a "thank you" situation!
何してるんですかほんとに
What on earth are you doing?
本当に痛かったんだぞマジで。
It really hurt, I'm serious.
マジで痛い。
It seriously hurts.
ねぇ痛いですよね？
It hurts, doesn't it?
４回もくらってんでしょ？
You got zapped four times, right?
４回くらった。
Four times.
とんでもねぇよ。
That's outrageous.
そのうち癖になりますよ。
You'll get addicted to it.
なんねぇよ！
No, I won't!
痛かったぜフブキ。
That hurt, Fubuki.
痛かったぜ。見てて怖かったよ。
It hurt. It was scary to watch.
それではフブキ先輩、選んでください。
Well then, Fubuki-senpai, make your choice.
うーん。ここはね、確実にイスを潰しておきたい。
Hmm. I want to definitely eliminate a chair here.
ああ、少なくしとくってことでね。
Ah, to reduce the number of choices.
ウチ当たりたくない。イスを確実に減らすってなるとここ。
I don't want to get hit. To surely eliminate a chair, it's gotta be here.
ここ、３！
Here, number 3!
多分こっち。
Probably this one.
ではどうぞ。
Go ahead.
本当にそれでいいのかしら、白上フブキ。
Are you really okay with that, Shirakami Fubuki?
うぉー！やったー！
Whoa! I did it!
ちくしょー！
Damn it!
まあちょっとひよってますね～
Well, she's chickening out a bit, isn't she?
え、これ違うよ。人のフリしてる…
Hey, that's not it. She's just pretending...
しかも絶対今、怖がってなかった。
What's more, she wasn't scared at all just now.
「絶対にここは無い」って
She was thinking, "It's definitely not here."
人のフリをして…「わぁ！」って言ってたけど
She was just pretending... She said "Waa!" but...
「まぁここにはねぇだろ」って本当は思ってたんだ
She was really thinking, "Well, it's probably not here."
サイコパスじゃん
She's a psychopath.
あげるよもうその称号。
I'll grant you that title.
さてさて、選んでいきますか。
Well then, shall we choose?
選んでください。どちらに座りますか。
Please choose. Which one will you sit on?
はい。
Yes.
ミオの考えてることなんてお見通しや。
I can see right through what you're thinking, Mio.
ええ？！
What?!
お見通しなの？
You can see through me?
簡単だよ、ミオの思考なんても。
It's easy. I know how you think, Mio.
でもここはちゃんと高い点数取らないとなぁ～
But I have to get a high score here...
って思うじゃん？って思ってるけども、しかし？
That's what you think I'm thinking, but what if?
それで、さっきの自分の行動を見て
So, looking at your previous action...
「ちっちゃい点数でもいいかも～！」
You're thinking, 'A small score might be fine!'
「だって倍宣言があるから！」って思ってんだよ～う！
'Because I can declare double points!' That's what you think!
めっちゃ盛り上がってるなぁ…。
She's getting so hyped up...
一人でめっちゃ盛り上がってる。
All by herself, she's so hyped.
ひどいね…。今すごい全部言うてる。
That's mean... She's saying everything I'm thinking...
ミオにうちあってるんだ。
She's really getting me.
みこのときと全然違います。
This is completely different from Miko's turn.
じゃあ、うちは11にしたいと思います。
Okay, then I think I'll choose 11.
いいのか本当に。
Are you really sure?
はい。
Yes.
いいですか？
Are you sure?
はい。
Yes.
ではフブキ先輩、電撃をどうぞ。
Then, Fubuki-senpai, press the button.
ミオ…！か！
Mio...! Agh!
痛い！
It hurts!
やったー！
YES!
これあるぞ！3連続あるぞ！
This might happen! Three in a row!
痛い！
It hurts!
すいちゃんごめーん！
Sui-chan, I'm sorry!
こんなに痛いなんて…。
I didn't think it would hurt this much...
これが痛みだっ！
This is pain!
いやー！
Nooo!
よっしゃー！一回ぐらい当てたいなぁ。
Alright! I wanna get it right at least once.
ミオ神のふわふわしっぽに…
On Mio-gami's fluffy tail...
やだ！
No!
さあ、頑張ってください。交代でいきましょう。
Okay, good luck. Let's switch places.
頑張ります。
I'll do my best.
ではミオ先輩、ずいぶん痛そうですけど、どちらに仕掛けるか決めてください。
Okay Mio-senpai, you seem in pain, but pick a trap.
ちょっと待って、2連続ってことでしょ、うちが。
Wait, that's two in a row for me.
やばすぎる。ケツが持たないよ、もう。
This is too much. My butt can't take it.
大丈夫、お尻は2コあるんでね。
It's okay, you have two butt cheeks.
ちょっと待って、あの、割れてるのを1個2個って換算するのやめてよ！
Wait, stop counting my split cheeks as one and two!
2個です。
Two!
その換算方法いったい何なの？
What kind of counting method is that?!
ルーレットじゃん、これ。
This is just roulette.
ケツっていう玉がどこに落ち着くか。
It's about where the ball called 'butt' lands.
ケツ来い！ケツ来い！ケツ来ぉいッ！
Come on, butt! Come on, butt! Come on, buuutt!
こっちに座ったせいで、こっちに仕掛ける可能性が出てしまったのはやっちまったかな。
Sitting here created a new possibility... I might've messed up.
まあ、でも可能性はありますからね。
Well, there's still a possibility.
まあ、確かに可能性しかない。
Well yeah, it's nothing but possibilities.
10！
Ten!
お！
Oh!
10！
Ten!
10？
Ten?
座りましたね。
She sat down.
では行きます。怖い！
Okay, here we go. I'm scared!
10！
Ten!
セーフ！
Safe!
うわー、10かー！
Aww, it was 10!
うわ、返り討ちにあった。
Ugh, she got me back.
くそー！俺はいつもそうだ！
Damn it! This always happens to me!
自分の心を信じろって言ったのに。
And I just said to trust my gut...
痛い！なんだよお前！ずるいんだよお前！
Painful! What the heck, you! You're cheating!
ずるいんだから、信じるよ。
Because you cheat, I'll believe you.
フブキはこっちに座ったか。
So Fubuki sat over here, huh?
今、ズズってしたな今。
You just made a "zuzu" sound just now.
どこどこどこ。
Where, where, where?
うちは、えーっと、そっちだ。4に仕掛けました。
I'm going with... that one. I set it on 4.
うわぁ、こわ！
Whoa, scary!
さぁ25ポイントになりましたフブさん。
Alright, Fubuki now has 25 points.
ミオちゃんは0ポイントだけど
Mio-chan has 0 points, but...
まあ、とりあえず当てることができれば
well, for now, if she can just guess correctly,
いくらでも逆転できるから。
she can turn it around anytime.
確かにね。
That's true.
後攻 大神ミオ
Second Player: Ookami Mio
それでは、運命の選択、どうぞ。
Well then, make your fateful choice. Please.
来いミオ！
Come at me, Mio!
お前を3回ブチ当ててやんだ！
I'll get you three times!
心が痛いけど…！
It hurts my heart, but...!
お前に、お前に心なんか無いだろ！
You... You don't have a heart!
2回もブチ当てておいて！
After getting me twice already!
バレてる
She knows.
バレてるw
She knows, lol
畜生だってバレてるんだ。
She knows you're a beast.
そんなことはない
That's not true.
ウチのことを思いやる心なんて1コも無いんだ！
You don't have an ounce of consideration for me!
そんなことないよ！
That's not true!
ミオのお尻のことも大切に思ってるよ。
I care about your butt, too.
嘘だろ、嘘だ！
That's a lie! A lie!
嘘じゃない！
It's not a lie!
じゃあ言うよ。仕掛けたのは11番だ。
Alright, I'll tell you. I set it on number 11.
え？え？え？
Huh? Huh? Huh?
ミオのお尻を守るために、白上はここで宣言するよ。
To protect Mio's butt, Shirakami declares right here,
11番に仕掛けたんだ。
that I set it on number 11.
でも、あの、次から2倍になるので、
But, um, the points double from the next round,
ちょっと高い点数は残しておきたいなって思うので、
so I want to leave the high-scoring numbers,
どうかな？
What do you think?
あえてちょっと低めに行きたいと思います。
So I think I'll dare to go for a lower number.
いい？
Are you sure?
7！ラッキーセブン！これでいく！
Seven! Lucky seven! I'm going with this!
はぁ〜
Haaa~
それでは、
Well then,
3回目の痛みだよ。
This is the third time it'll hurt.
もう帰れないもん。もう帰れない。
I can't go back now. I can't go back.
電撃をどうぞ。
Please begin the shock.
くらえー！
Take this!
あー、怖い！
Aah, scary!
やったー！くっそー！くそ！くそー！
Yes! Dammit! Damn! Dammit!
しかもちゃんと宣言通りに11に仕掛けてた。
And she really did set it on 11, just like she said.
優しさだ！優しさ見せたよ。
That's kindness! I showed you my kindness.
ウチの尻は守られた。
My butt was protected.
そうだよ、守られたよ。
That's right, it was protected.
うそ！ヒヒヒ...座れんかなって思ってた。
Lies! Hehe... I was thinking maybe you couldn't sit.
くっそー！怖いよ。
Dammit! It's scary.
これで25対7になりましたけれども、
With this, the score is 25 to 7, but...
次からね、4ラウンド目が始まりますので、
from the next, the 4th round begins, so...
そうだよ。
That's right.
倍宣言をどうするんですか？
What will you do about the double-points declaration?
倍にするの？
Are you going to double it?
倍宣言します！
I declare double points!
わー！はい！
Wow! Okay!
倍宣言いただきました！やばい、面白
We have a double-points declaration! Whoa, this is fun-
倍宣言おもろいな。
Declaring double points is fun.
倍宣言おもろい。
なんで正座したの？
Why did you sit seiza-style?
ちょっとケツが痛くなってきた。
My butt started to hurt a little.
2回だったもんね？
It was twice, right?
2回、そう。まだ負傷してるケツが。
Twice, yes. Her butt is still injured.
先攻 白上フブキ
First Player: Shirakami Fubuki
フブキ、1回ぐらい食らってみよう。
Fubuki, let's try getting shocked at least once.
やだ。
No.
1回ぐらい、食らってみようよ。
Just once, let's try it.
清く
For purity's sake.
それではフブキ先輩、選んでください。
Well then, Fubuki-senpai, please choose.
きよた…やだ。
Purity... no.
1回ぐらいね。
Just once.
やだ。
No.
おすすめ。
A recommendation.
おすすめ。ウチのおすすめ。
A recommendation. My recommendation.
おすすめ。おすすめは何番？
Recommendation. What number do you recommend?
えー、やっぱ1かな？みこさんと一緒で
Hmm, maybe 1? Same as Miko-san.
じゃほな、1か
Well then, number 1?
バカヤロウ！
You idiot!
倍宣言で1座るやつなんかおらん！
Nobody would pick 1 after I doubled the points!
そうだ！
That's right!
そんなん選ぶ人いないですよ。
No one would choose that.
おい、なんでみこにチクチクすんの？
Hey, why are you taking a jab at me?
ここでもそこでも言ってた！
You were saying it both here and there!
すいちゃんが「自分を信じろ」って言ってたから
Suichan said "Believe in yourself," so...
11を。
I'll pick 11.
迷ってる。
She's hesitating.
すい、自分を信じていいのかすい。
Sui, can I really believe in myself, Sui?
1回ぐらい食らっとけ。
Just get zapped once already.
フブキさん、信じて。
Fubuki-san, believe.
すい。
Sui.
今、星街が宿った。
Now, Hoshimachi has possessed me.
僕が星だ…！
I am the star...!
終わりましたね。
It's over.
どうなるのかな。
I wonder what will happen.
灰になるまで踊ってよ。
Dance until I turn to ash.
やだ、こわい。
No, I'm scared.
電撃をどうぞ。
Go ahead and press the button.
はい。フブキ、
Okay. Fubuki,
お前も1回ぐらい食らえ！
you get zapped for once too!
すごい！
Amazing!
ダメ。
No way.
6番に座りなさい、あなたは。
You, go sit on number 6.
宿るな！おい星街宿るな！
Don't possess her! Hey, Hoshimachi, don't possess her!
うわー！悔しい！
Ugh! So frustrating!
悔しい…もう…あんなこと言わなければよかった。
Frustrating... I shouldn't have said that.
言ってしまったな…「自分を信じろ」なんて。
You had to go and say it... "Believe in yourself."
つまり？今？ということは？
So? Now? That means?
22ポイント獲得したので、
She got 22 points,
なんと47ポイントになりました！
bringing her to a total of 47 points!
うわー！
Yay!
本当に仕掛けられてない。
It wasn't really rigged.
あー、びっくりした。
Ahh, that surprised me.
これで戦争は終わりってことですか？
Does this mean the war is over?
そうだよ！誰がこんなひどい戦いをしようって言ったんだ！
That's right! Who suggested such a terrible battle?!
お前じゃないのか？
Wasn't it you?
そうですよね？
That's right, isn't it?
違う…白上は違うんだ…
No... Shirakami is different...
ええ？
Huh?
白上は「やろう！」って言われたから巻き取っただけなんだ！
When they said "Let's do it!", I just went along with it!
もしかして…黒幕がいるってコト！？
Could it be... there's a mastermind?!
そうだ！どこだ、黒幕！
That's right! Where is the mastermind?!
どこにいるんだ！
Where are they?!
え？
Huh?
ウチらのせいにしてるよ？
Are they blaming us?
ということで、優勝はフブキ先輩です！
And with that, the winner is Fubuki-senpai!
やったー！
Yay!
あー、一回も食らわなかった。
Ahh, I didn't get zapped even once.
どういうことなんですかね、この戦いの結末って。
What's the deal with the outcome of this battle?
呼んだのこの白上フブキさんですよね？
The one who called us here was Shirakami Fubuki, right?
違います。
No, it's not.
本当に。
Really.
人のフリをしているキツネ。
A fox pretending to be human.
なんでやねん！
Why you!
悪魔？
A devil?
運が良かったってこと。
She was just lucky.
これが畜生なんだ。
This is what a beast is.
いや、どうですか、フブキ先輩、今のお気持ちは。
So, how are you feeling now, Fubuki-senpai?
いや、1回も当たらずにできたってことはですね、
Well, the fact that I made it without getting hit once,
今年はやっぱ運がついてるということなんですね、2025年。
means that this year, 2025, is my lucky year.
いいな、運。いや、よかったよかった。
Lucky you. Well, that's good.
その笑顔、いつまで保っていられるかですけどね。
I wonder how long you can keep that smile, though.
なんなんなん、なんなんですか？優勝したのに。
What, what, what is it? Even though I won.
調子こいてるんでしょ、これ。
She's getting carried away, isn't she?
はいはいはい。余裕ぶっこいちゃって。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Acting all nonchalant.
怒ってる？強制的に座らされる、もしかして？
Are you angry? Am I being forced to sit down?
電気椅子に？そんなことはしませんよ。まさかまさか。
On the electric chair? No way, we wouldn't do that.
ほんまか？
Really?
ということで、見てください。でーん！
With that, please take a look. Ta-da!
おお、2択ある。
Oh, two choices.
2分1です。2分1。
It's 1 in 2. 1 in 2.
どちらかが王者の椅子です。
One of them is the champion's chair.
2分の1で電撃をくらわなければ本物の王者として認められる
If you don't get shocked with a 1/2 chance, you'll be acknowledged as the true champion.
そうそうそう。
That's right.
それはもう心の底から称えられるよ、うちらだってね。
Then we can praise you from the bottom of our hearts.
私たちはまだ認めない。
We don't acknowledge it yet.
まだ諦めない。
We haven't given up.
あなたがもがき苦しんでいる姿を
I want to see your face writhing in agony.
何度もね、うん。いつも戦ってますから。
We've fought so many times.
いや、私はね、フブさんはね、こっちに座れると思う。
No, I think Fubuki-san will sit here.
ああ！なぜなら
Ah! Because...
なぜなら...
Because...
欲張りキツネ。
the greedy fox...
欲張り...。でかいからね。
A greedy fox... - You are huge, after all.
そうそうそう、そうですね。確かに。
Right. That's true.
え、みこさん的にはどっちだと思う？どっちがお勧め？
What about you, Miko-san? Which one do you recommend?
みこさん的には、すいちゃんと同じになりたいと思う。
From my perspective... I want to agree with Sui-chan.
そんなにおすすめ？ - 11。
You recommend it that much? - Number 11.
11？ - あえて11。
11? - I'll take a chance on 11.
みこベットばらばらと。 - 12のおすすめ。
Your bets are all over the place. - We recommend 12 and 11.
じゃあみこさん、信じとくか。 - うん。
Then I'll trust Miko-san. - Okay.
お！信じとく。 - 信じてもいいんですか？
Okay. I'll trust you. - You'll trust me? - Can I really trust you?
信じてください！
You can trust me! - Please trust me!
信じますか？ - 信じてください。
I'll trust you! - Please trust me.
信じてあげよう。
I'll believe you!
それでは、運命の選択。
Alright then. Your fateful choice.
電気をどうぞ！
Now, turn on the electricity!
（悲鳴）
(Screaming)
信じてください！
Please believe me!
私を信じておけばよかったのに！
You should have trusted me!
12が正解だったのか！ - ひどいことをしたな！
You did a terrible thing! - So 12 was the right one!
フブメットさんの絆崩壊。
The bond of FubuMet is broken!
こっちだったのか、12だったのか！
It was this one! It was 12!
ありがとう！信じてくれて！
Thank you! For believing me!
場所がさすがにさ、フブちゃんに当てるに決まってるじゃん！
It's obvious that the seat was rigged to shock Fubuki.
とんでもねえやつだてめえ！ - くそ！
You're a terrible person! - You're terrible!
みこさんの言ってた通りだわ。中に人いるわ。
It's just as Miko-san said. There's someone inside.
※中に人は入っておりません
※ There is no one inside.
本当だね。- すごかったよ。すごいよね、勢いはね。
It's true. - It was amazing. The force was incredible.
よかったね。これで全員電気を味わえたということで。
Good. Now everyone has experienced the electric shock.
感想いってきますか？
Shall we hear your thoughts?
そうですね。じゃあ、すいちゃんから一言お願いしますか？
Alright. Sui-chan, would you like to start?
はい。えー、私わかりました。このゲーム、
Yes. Okay, I understand now. In this game,
疑心暗鬼になった者から負ける。
the one who becomes suspicious loses.
己を信じられなくなった者から負けていく。
The one who can't believe in themselves is the one who loses.
フブキは己の事を最後まで信じた。だからこそ勝った。
Fubuki believed in herself until the very end, so she won.
私は“敗北者”じゃけぇ...!!!
I'm... a loser...!
自分で言うことないよ？
You don't have to say that yourself.
敗北者じゃけぇ。ありがとうございます。
I'm a loser. Thank you.
じゃあ次、みこさん。
Miko-san.
はい。えー、フブミコメットさんでね、3人でさ、色々さ、うんうん、話してた時にやりたいねっつって、始まったけど。
Yes. FubuMikoMet, the three of us talked about wanting to do this
いやー、こんなに痛いとは。
Yeah... I didn't think it would hurt this much.
ね、こんなに痛いとは。それはそう。
I know. It really hurts.
フブさん、ぜひね、他のホロメンにも
Fubuki-san, I really hope you make the other Holo members
味わってほしい。- うんうんうんうんうん。- その気持ちになります。
feel this too. - We all have that feeling now.
なるほどね。- はい。
I see. - Yes.
まあ次あったら、みこさんは呼ばなくて大丈夫です。
Well, if there's a next time, you don't need to invite me.
まあまあ、味わったからね、もうね。
Well, you've had a taste, so...
ありがとうございました。じゃあ次、りっか。
Thank you. Alright, next up is Rikka.
はい。いや、もうこの中で1人、
Yes. I'm the only one here...
1人で4回も電気を食らって、- 確かに。
who's been zapped four times. - That's right.
いや、本当ですよ。もう今お尻がちょっと逆に求めてますからね？
I mean, my butt is actually kind of asking for it, you know?
ええー！？ 電気も… あ、座る？
Huh?! The electricity... Ah, sit down?
あ、いやだいやだいやだ！大丈夫ですけど。
Ah, no, no, no, no, no! It's fine though.
フリじゃないんだ…
It's not just a bit...
そうなんだ。
That's right.
いや、これからまでちょっと本当に、ま、今みこ先輩言ってましたけど
Well, from now on, really, as Miko-senpai just said,
いろんなホロメンさんにこの電気の味知ってほしいと思います。
I want various Holomems to know the taste of this electricity.
でもトワも呼ばないでください。
But please don't invite Towa again.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
じゃ、続いてミオ！ はい！
Next up, Mio! Yes!
なんかね、とんでもない地獄に巻き込まれた。
You know, I got dragged into a ridiculous hell.
なんか久しぶりにこんなに、あの、本当に嫌だと思う地獄、
It's been a long time since I've been in a hell that I truly...
本当に久しぶりでした！
...I really, truly hated!
本当に嫌だった。マジで… 確かにそう。
It was really awful. Seriously... That's true.
これエンタメ考えらんねえわ。ちょっと守りに行かしてもらうわ。
I can't think about entertainment. I'm just gonna be defensive.
いやでも、ここはエンタメ的にこれやったらどうかなとかね、
No, but you have to think, for entertainment's sake,
色々考えちゃうじゃんね。
"what if I did this?" and stuff, right?
ねえ。もうガチの地獄でした。
Right. It was a genuine hell.
本当に怖かった。 マジで怖かった。
It was really scary. Seriously scary.
これを乗り越えたらね、めちゃくちゃ強くなれると思うので
If you overcome this, I think you'll become super strong,
是非他のホロメンにもやっていただきたいなと思いました。
so I'd love for other Holomems to try it too.
地獄に？
Into hell?
地獄って言ってんのに誘ってやがる。
She's inviting them even though she calls it hell.
では… フブキさん、お返しします。 はい！
Well then... Fubuki-san, back to you. Yes!
フブキは優勝したんですけど、え、最後当たっちゃいましたけども。
Fubuki was the winner, but, well, I got shocked in the end.
これを見て興味を持ったそこのホロメン！
To the Holomem out there watching who got interested!
次はキミだ！
Next, it's you!
次はお前だ！
覚悟しろ。 オールマ〇ト？
Prepare yourself. All M*ght?
オールマイト。 次は君だ！
All Might. Next, it's you!
次はお前！ はい！
Next, you! Yes!
はい！電気椅子ゲーム司会は白上でした！ありがとうございました！
Yes! For the Electric Chair Game, your MC was Shirakami! Thank you!
わー！
Yay!